<VillagerDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/VillagerDialog VillagerDialog.xsd" id="602042" huntingZoneId="0" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/VillagerDialog">
    <Text id="1" endSocial="0">
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">1. Written by: Marphin&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;font color='#800040'&gt;- The sky is clear. I can smell something burning.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;font color='#800040'&gt;- Number of refugees increased greatly from the Valley of Titans. Additional supplies are needed.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;font color='#004080'&gt;[Details]&lt;/font&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Pora Elinu is trying to restore Popolion by naturalizing the refugees. Supplies are running out, but the queen said that Seren promised that this year's harvest will be rich. Yiyahu said that would change nothing and left for Velika.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I took the guards out to hunt for game. We need more supplies. Someone named Jelena helped us. We got more than we expected thanks to her. I never thought that a Castanic would be so friendly.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Maybe only female Castanics are...?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">5. Written by: Marphin&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;font color='#800040'&gt;- The sky is cloudy. Unnatural. Clouds are dark red.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;font color='#800040'&gt;- Unknown energy detected. Asked Bedoram to investigate the energy.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;font color='#004080'&gt;[Details]&lt;/font&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The strange rocks on the hill almost smell like blood. According to Korwyn, they are mana stones that the Vampir use for decoration. He also told me that the stones are not natural.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The duke and duchess denied any involvement. They insisted they would investigate each of the Vampir families on their own. They gave the refugees invitations to a party, at which they said the refugees can have their fill.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The giant carrot cake looked delicious, but I'm the supply officer! I couldn't go to such a party. Hmm!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;(The next page is burnt.)&lt;PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;Previous page.&lt;/PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close the book.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">11. Written by: Marphin&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;font color='#800040'&gt;- The sky is cloudy. Still dark red.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;font color='#800040'&gt;- Second day of the rescue operation.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;font color='#004080'&gt;[Details]&lt;/font&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Charging through the front door of the Sinestral Manor was a failure. Jelena told us that the refugees escaped through the back. That was a relief.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;(The page is burnt.)&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I always thought that the vampirs, duke, and duchess were nice. But now I know that &amp;quot;invited to a party&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;letting someone have their fill&amp;quot; are very different.&lt;PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;Previous page.&lt;/PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close the book.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">13. Written by: Marphin&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;font color='#800040'&gt;- The sky is clear. Clouds are back to normal.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;font color='#800040'&gt;- Supply base has shut down. Troops returned to Popolion.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;font color='#004080'&gt;[Details]&lt;/font&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I had a nightmare. Blood poured out from the front door of the manor. I wonder if it was really a dream. I was able to recognize faces of the recruits. They were former refugees. Then huge vampir eyes glared at Popolion.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Jelena tried her best to protect us, but many valuables were burnt. I was able to gather important and classified documents during the retreat. Are the reinforcement from Pora Elinu even coming?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;(The ink is smudged, changing color from black to brown.)&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I can smell blood everywhere. I can hear voices on the wind.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Delah Gluda, Delah Gluda...&lt;PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;Previous page.&lt;/PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close the book.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
</VillagerDialog>
