<VillagerDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/VillagerDialog VillagerDialog.xsd" id="45305" huntingZoneId="0" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/VillagerDialog">
    <Text id="1" endSocial="0">
        <Page social="0">A Princess at War, by Princess Syona&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Introduction, by Ralak&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Princess Syona of the Popori Kingdom acted as a representative to the Valkyon Federation during the Argon War, speaking for the queen and occasionally for the goddess Seren herself.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;This account of her wartime experiences, from the first report of the invasion to the eventual victory at Kaiator, written by my hand, forms a vital part of federation history.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;—Karalak&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close the book.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">While Elleon, Hasmina, and I traveled in Southern Shara, we received a message from {@Rgn:72001} saying that creatures known as argons had attacked in the north and now occupied the region surrounding {@Rgn:84001}.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;{@Rgn:84001} itself still stood, of course, protected as it was by {@Creature:248#2008}'s shield—but for how much longer?&lt;PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;Previous page.&lt;/PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close the book.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">The argons had broken through the northern defenses and advanced quickly south, almost to the walls of Kaiator. The message described them as mechanical golems, but of a completely different order from anything we knew.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;They were certainly as relentless as golems, though far more powerful. And, while most seemed mindless, others possessed an eerie intelligence.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;No one knew where they had come from.&lt;PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;Previous page.&lt;/PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close the book.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">The queen asked me to represent the kingdom at a war congress in {@Rgn:63001}. Delegates representing many races attended to discuss their concerns about an invasion so near the amani capitol.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Seven races sent delegates to the human capitol to discuss a course of action. Commander Fraya represented the elves, while General Kaidun, who came with her from Allemantheia, spoke for the amani.&lt;PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;Previous page.&lt;/PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close the book.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">The meeting dragged on. Some insisted on sending a delegation to negotiate with the argons, while others argued for going immediately to Kaiator's defense.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;It was Velik who broke the stalemate, appearing before the congress in support of fielding a large and well-equipped army to counter this powerful alien threat.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;She warned that any enemy strong enough to overwhelm the amani forces and threaten Kaiator would eventually menace us all.&lt;PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;Previous page.&lt;/PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close the book.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">In the end we agreed to send our armies. There was no Valkyon Federation, and no coordinated command of forces.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Eventually, the leadership and wisdom of General Catharnach would lead to the creation of the federation, but at that time we were a handful of separate nations, not far removed from warring with one another.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We had little or no cohesion and no real plan of action except to get our troops to Northern Shara. So that's what we did.&lt;PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;Previous page&lt;/PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close the book.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">With Northern Shara occupied by the argons and pegasus transport disabled, we needed to establish communication and transportation between Velika and the war zone. Establishing secure teleportals at both ends would be crucial to fast action, and that depended on having someone in Northern Shara. At present, with Kaiator effectively cut off, we had no one.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Elleon–ever the bold one–volunteered to lead the infiltration.&lt;PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;Previous page.&lt;/PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close the book.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Elleon asked me to join his infiltration team, to which I assented eagerly. Hasmina had already volunteered, of course. Like Elleon, she never ran from a challenge.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We recruited the rest from the best of a crowd of enthusiastic candidates. Within three days we departed for Northern Shara with teleportals and a flight stone attuned to Allemantheia—where the armies already gathered.&lt;PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;Previous page.&lt;/PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close the book.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">On the way north we encountered a band of free sikandaris who'd been evading the argons thus far. I knew a bit of their language, and translated for the rest.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The sikandari said they knew the location of Amena Quatla, Sikander's legendary lost city. After speaking with Elleon and I for some time, they agreed to break the seal that had hidden the city from sight for so long.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Now we would have a base from which to strike the argons.&lt;PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;Previous page.&lt;/PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close the book.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">The argons could not anticipate this plan. The very land from which we would attack would not even exist in this world until the sikandari unsealed it.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We placed the flight stone in Susurrus Woods, creating a pegasus route from Allemantheia, and set up enough teleportals to bring in our troops and supplies.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;When all was in place, our armies moved out for Kaiator and victory.&lt;PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;Previous page.&lt;/PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close the book.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Relieving Kaiator cost us greatly, and it was not the end of the war. However, it was the kind of victory that sets hearts afire, and from that fire we forged alliances.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Other armies would fight other battles, and still more battles yet remain to be fought. But on this day, Kaiator—Kaia's unbroken iron shield—shone as a beacon that still glows in the hearts of all who continue to fight for freedom, and for life itself, against the argon invaders.&lt;PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;Previous page.&lt;/PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close the book.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">After Kaiator, we went our separate ways—Elleon to Allemantheia, Hasmina to some other part of the argon front. I turned back towards Seeliewood to help heal the land the argons had nearly destroyed.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;When I had been back for some time, I had a dream. Seren appeared to me at the Lake of Tears and crowned me Princess of the Black Lands.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;When I awoke, I took the road north again, toward the devastation, toward the fighting, toward the place where history will be made.&lt;PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;Previous page.&lt;/PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close the book.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
</VillagerDialog>
