<VillagerDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/VillagerDialog VillagerDialog.xsd" id="45338" huntingZoneId="0" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/VillagerDialog">
    <Text id="1" endSocial="0">
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">Concerning the exact mechanism for argonifying living things, we have many theories and few facts.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We now know the Three Towers is where the argons were carrying out their unspeakable experiments in transforming all life to their version of life.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;PCNAME&gt;'s help in routing the argons from the towers themselves will buy us time to learn more.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Next Page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close the journal.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">It appears the argons used this place to research the growth and development of plants and animals around the world. We have no idea why these intruders were researching plants...but I must figure it out. We've failed to discover many records of their research, but one thing I did find is they designed this place to be a Mysterium of their own. To be honest, their methods are most efficient...but extremely unethical. This kind of research should not take place at all. These creatures we're up against...&lt;PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;Previous Page.&lt;/PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Next Page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close the journal.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">Judging from their hierarchic society, the argons act with a single purpose, as if they were an army or a hive. However, the so called Ramayans I discovered at this tower, seem to be a more highly intelligent creature compared to the other argons.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Despite their origins, they actually think logically and adapt strategies to meet their needs.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I assume the Ramayans analyzed their creation, modified it, and tried to apply that to other species of the world. Their high intelligence...&lt;PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;Previous Page.&lt;/PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Next Page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close the journal.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">To my surprise, the phenomenon we named argonization or argonomorph appears to be an accident. It seems the Ramayans were attempting to convert organic matter into energy. Their research was proceeding toward that point when their paradigm of thought shifted. This appears to be evidence that the argons can self-synthesize. There's no doubt their research was brutal.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Their research speaks of circumventing Arun and Shara, and all our Gods...how can that even be...&lt;PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;Previous Page.&lt;/PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Next Page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close the journal.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">I was able to reach deep in the tower with &lt;PCNAME&gt;'s help. Since the argons here were taken care of, I have high hopes that my research will proceed with no troubles. I was able to witness an argon capsule. That definitely aided my research results, outlining what these creatures truly are.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The argons are no longer 'unknown' to us.&lt;PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;Previous Page.&lt;/PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close the journal.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
</VillagerDialog>
