<VillagerDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/VillagerDialog VillagerDialog.xsd" id="207641" huntingZoneId="0" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/VillagerDialog">
    <Text id="1" endSocial="0">
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">Welcome, hero!&lt;BR&gt;.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The Valkyon Federation always tries its best to support its operatives, and has many benefits in store for you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Please keep up the good work.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;May the blessings of the goddess be upon you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;B&gt;&lt;font color = '#FF0000'&gt;This note has no effect on XP gains or quest progression, and you may destroy it after reading it.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/B&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Ecologist Lenarive has collected information on the ecosystem, history, and environment of our rapidly changing world in the form of collectable cards. &lt;BR&gt;Card fragments containing this information can be found just about everywhere. Once you assemble a card, register it to your Card Collection, and you'll gain a small bonus specific to that card.&lt;BR&gt;You can open your Card Collection (Shift + B) through the helm-shaped My Character menu. Bring the cursor over a card's image, and you can check its background story, abilities, and where you can obtain it.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Collect cards to raise the level of your Card Collection, which increases the number of cards of the same type you can equip, and the maximum cost of cards you can equip.&lt;BR&gt;You can also activate various Collection Effects, which you can check under the Collection Effects tab.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Card fragments can be obtained by hunting monsters, completing quests, by gathering or fishing, or can be purchased with Reputation points. You can also find cards posted by other players in the Trade Broker.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Put away the note.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
</VillagerDialog>
