<VillagerDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/VillagerDialog VillagerDialog.xsd" id="45340" huntingZoneId="0" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/VillagerDialog">
    <Text id="1" endSocial="0">
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">Summary of Consos Clan History, as Told by Nandu, Consos Guardian of Vision&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We lost our history the day Balder died. His death throes tore apart Balder's archives—once a single great edifice—and the very ground on which it rested. Only a few children survived. I was one of them.&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close book.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" endSocial="0">
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">The adults spoke often of Balder, how troubled his face was, how infrequently he laughed. Lok visited him frequently. I think Balder's moodiness frustrated him; Lok was always chiding him or jollying him out of his moods.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I never saw Lok without a smile until...that day. &lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close book.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3" endSocial="0">
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">I remember the sound, a tearing roar like thunder that wouldn't end. My father, Bornu, told me we had to flee. As he carried me through the lighthouse plaza, I saw Lok laboring over a smoking arcane device with a team of castanics. His skin was ashen, his eyes wild with grief and fear.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;There was another man, also—a shadowy man with a pointed beard. He was smiling. &lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close book.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4" endSocial="0">
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">Our parents hid us in the archive's great vaults. I'm sure they meant to return, but moments after they closed the doors, the ground shook like a wet mugato, again and again, hurling us from floor to wall to ceiling. I was near-deafened by the sound and near dead from the impact. The vault doors lay askew.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Through the gap I saw an immense figure wreathed in blue flame using his burning hands to close a great rip in the fabric of the sky. Balder.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close book.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">We were rescued, fed, clothed...by the gods, for all others were forbidden entrance. I remember them arguing by Lok's great spear, fallen near the archives. None of them stayed long, except Mystel.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;After my hearing returned, she taught me to use the repositories and explained my duties as leader of my tribe.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I was nine years old.&lt;PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;Previous page.&lt;/PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close book.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">To your other queries, I answer: we guard Balder's legacy but do not control it. You are welcome to explore the refuge, but do so humbly; this is holy ground, and its secrets protect themselves.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;If you wish, as I do, to unlock the final secret Balder bequeathed us, help me to find those worthy to seek it. Only when Balder's conditions are met will all our curiosity be satisfied.&lt;PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;Previous page.&lt;/PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close book.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
</VillagerDialog>
