<VillagerDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/VillagerDialog VillagerDialog.xsd" id="207639" huntingZoneId="0" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/VillagerDialog">
    <Text id="1" endSocial="0">
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">Welcome to Arborea!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The Valkyon Federation always endeavors to equip its guardians well for battle, and has many benefits in store for you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Please keep up the good work for Arborea.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;May the blessings of the goddess Kaia be upon you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;B&gt;&lt;font color = '#FF0000'&gt;This note has no effect on XP gains or quest progression, and you may destroy it after reading it.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/B&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Skill Advancement: When your character reaches level 66, the Skill Advancement tab (K) will be activated, and they start earning Skill Advancement XP to advance their skills.&lt;BR&gt;You can obtain Skill Advancement Books/Optimization Scrolls and Complete Skill Advancement Books/Optimization Scrolls through special events or the TERA Store, and use them to optimize or advance your skills without having to spend Gold or materials. Skill Advancement Level is capped at 180.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;B&gt;&lt;font color = '#FF0000'&gt;Caution: Skill Advancement can't be unlocked unless you learn all available skills at their maximum levels. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/B&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Skill Advancement (Lv. 66, 68, 70)&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Use Skill Advancement Books (I, II, or III) and Skill Advancement Points to advance your skills to level 60.&lt;BR&gt;Skill Advancement is highly recommended for your character's growth because it gradually enhances your skills and grants additional stats.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Skill Optimization (Lv. 67, 69)&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Use scrolls for Skill Optimization I-II and Gold to activate 3 skill options. You can use one of the activated options. There are special options for PvE and PvP. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Skill Advancement Scrolls (unlock option) are available in the following locations:&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;[Dungeons]&lt;BR&gt;Gossamer Vault (Easy), Akalath Quarantine, Ruinous Manor (Easy)&lt;BR&gt;[Exodor Daily Quests]&lt;BR&gt;Obtainable as a reward for daily quests. You can also use Exodor Reputation to buy scrolls.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Put away the note.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
</VillagerDialog>
