<VillagerDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/VillagerDialog VillagerDialog.xsd" id="207638" huntingZoneId="0" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/VillagerDialog">
    <Text id="1" endSocial="0">
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">Welcome, hero!&lt;BR&gt;.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The Valkyon Federation always tries its best to support its operatives, and has many benefits in store for you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Please keep up the good work.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;May the blessings of the goddess be upon you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;B&gt;&lt;font color = '#FF0000'&gt;This note has no effect on XP gains or quest progression, and you may destroy it after reading it.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/B&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Use your Federation Supply: Glyph Tokens to buy all the available Glyphs available in the Token Shop.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Learn all the Glyphs you've bought, then open the Skills window (K) and select "Recommended Glyphs." Recommended Glyphs are optimized for PvE mode, and are comprised of useful options for exploring dungeons and hunting monsters.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You can register up to five sets of glyphs to handle different PvE or PvP situation, and switch between them at any time you are not in combat.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;EP: You can further customize your skills by eanring and spending EP. To start, you have 20 EP assigned to Mighty Attack.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You can change your EP settings through the the helm-shaped My Character menu. Shift-click to allocate 20 EP at a time.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Please read the descriptions of your main skills and invest your EP carefully.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;EP can also be saved on each page to be used in different situations, e.g., PvE and PvP. EP that you’ve invested by mistake can be restored with EP Reset Potions. You have been provided with 2 EP Reset Potions in this tutorial. You can also puchase more from Specialty Stores in Highwatch, Velika, and other big cities.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Put away the note.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
</VillagerDialog>
