<VillagerDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/VillagerDialog VillagerDialog.xsd" id="6001" huntingZoneId="739" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/VillagerDialog">
    <Text id="1" endSocial="0">
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">You found someone's journal. Apparently, this was Hennika's diary, when she was still a child.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" endSocial="0">
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">Detrian is gone. He made a wooden doll for me, and I still keep it in my bed.&lt;BR&gt;I feel strange. Detrian’s stuff is here, but he is gone.&lt;BR&gt;His clothes are still here. His sword is here. But Detrian is not here.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I wonder what happens to people when they die. I wonder what happened to my brother.&lt;TEXTBUTTON&gt;Open the journal.&lt;/TEXTBUTTON&gt;&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Looks like Hennika was crying when she wrote this."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">I want to be grown up like my brother and save people. I practice swordfighting everyday.&lt;BR&gt;Every time I practice, I think of Detrian. It makes me sad.&lt;BR&gt;Detrian once told me that, after I grow up, I can use a real sword, not a practice sword made of wood.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I miss my brother.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Hm...there's more."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">I made a friend today.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I was heading to the hill where Detrian and I used to go. Suddenly, a huge beast jumped out of the bushes.&lt;BR&gt;I turned and ran as fast as I could. I accidently dropped Detrian’s sword, but I had no time to pick it up.&lt;BR&gt;The beast came after me, and cornered me in a dead end.&lt;BR&gt;But the beast didn’t kill me. He had something in his mouth, and dropped it right in front of me.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;It was Detrian’s sword!&lt;BR&gt;I picked it up, but the monster just stared at me.&lt;BR&gt;Then strangely, I wasn't afraid anymore.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Hennika made friends with a monster?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">I was a good girl today.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I found a baby bird in the woods.&lt;BR&gt;I picked it up, and Argog put me on his shoulder so we could put it back in its nest.&lt;BR&gt;The tree was tall, but it didn’t stop us from returning the baby to his mother.&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;"She must have been so lonely."&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
</VillagerDialog>
