<VillagerDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/VillagerDialog VillagerDialog.xsd" id="45483" huntingZoneId="0" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/VillagerDialog">
    <Text id="1" endSocial="0">
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">&lt;BR&gt;It was a cold night. The holiday is normally filled with joy and happiness. But that day was different.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I couldn't help thinking that something wasn't right. And then, suddenly, Mutated Poporis were swarming our farm. The grownups went out and fought. My sister and I were too afraid to help, so we stayed inside.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The villagers didn't stand a chance. There were too many of them. Soon, the mutants got inside the house.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Read the next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">&lt;BR&gt;I couldn't move. My sister had to grab my hand and drag me to the back door.&lt;BR&gt;She threw me out the door and told me "Run! Don't look back!"&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I did what she said. I didn't look back. I just ran.&lt;BR&gt;But the mutants kept chasing me. I don't remember how long I kept running. I was getting tired and the mutants were getting closer.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Read the next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">Then, just as my legs gave out, it seemed as though the moonlight... shimmered. Almost as though the moon had shattered into pieces. But it wasn't the moon.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;A mutant fell down beside me, and before I knew it, they were all dead.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;When I recovered my wits, I found a runeglaive, along with a letter, just lying on the ground.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;"Just as the moonlight guided my path to you, I hope this runeglaive will help you."&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;As soon as I read the letter, I knew what I had to do. I grabbed the runeglaive and headed back.&lt;BR&gt;Back to Popolion.&lt;BR&gt;(The next page is torn out.)&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Quoted from [Valkyrie Journal], author unknown&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close the book.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
</VillagerDialog>
