<VillagerDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/VillagerDialog VillagerDialog.xsd" id="6002" huntingZoneId="739" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/VillagerDialog">
    <Text id="1" endSocial="0">
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">You found someone's journal. The refined handwriting suggests that Hennika was an adult when she made these entries.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" endSocial="0">
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">My belated homecoming. My old desk is covered with a thick layer of dust.&lt;BR&gt;Your clothes, though a bit moth-eaten, are still neatly folded away. I gently brushed them off, and put them back on your bed.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;May his soul rest in peace.&lt;TEXTBUTTON&gt;"Her journal is a letter to her brother."&lt;/TEXTBUTTON&gt;&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"There's more."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">Detrian, I still feel like the girl I was when I was twelve.&lt;BR&gt;I can still recall the anger I felt whenever I saw monsters...particularly those gulas.&lt;BR&gt;But I changed over time. I hope this doesn’t sound like I'm dishonoring your memory, but I don’t think I hate monsters anymore.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I’ve seen orcans who spoke a human language. They wanted to learn how to write, they wanted to be friends with humans. They are not savages that everyone perceives them to be.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Most importantly, I saw the real face of the Valkyon Federation. I saw them slaughtering peaceful orcans. Young ones, old ones, parents, even children.&lt;BR&gt;The federation sees them as nothing but animals.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Hmm..."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">Detrian, are we really better than monsters?&lt;BR&gt;Am I better than Argog because I have smaller teeth?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Those orcans were not looking for a fight. The federation soldiers, though...they murdered the orcans in cold blood.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;That was the same day I learned that I am not the only one who thinks this way.&lt;BR&gt;I saw a human casting healing spells for them.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;He didn’t even bat an eye when he saw Argog! The man is far from the ordinary.&lt;BR&gt;I asked his name, but he said he doesn’t have one any longer.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;He wants to make up for what the Valkyon Federation has done.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"I wonder who that man was...?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">Detrian, I finally found my true path in him.&lt;BR&gt;With him, I will become common folks’ protector, like I always wanted to be.&lt;BR&gt;True, the federation has done some good in the world. The hero who saved us when we were prisoners, who "almost" saved you—worked for the federation as well.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;But the Valkyon Federation does not always stand for justice. People suffered, and still suffer for its wrongdoing.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I will save them in my own way.&lt;BR&gt;Please have faith in me.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Damn, I miss you. Now I am a real swordfighter. I wish you were here to see me...&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;"The guardian? She means me."&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
</VillagerDialog>
