<VillagerDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/VillagerDialog VillagerDialog.xsd" id="207637" huntingZoneId="0" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/VillagerDialog">
    <Text id="1" endSocial="0">
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">Welcome, hero!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The Valkyon Federation always tries its best to support its operatives, and has many benefits in store for you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Please keep up the good work.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;May the blessings of the goddess be upon you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;B&gt;&lt;font color = '#FF0000'&gt;This note has no effect on XP gains or quest progression, and you may destroy it after reading it.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/B&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Items in TERA are generally classified into three categories: Gear, Accessory, and Miscellaneous. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Gear comes in four different types: Weapons, Body Armor, Hand Armor, and Foot Armor. The gear you wear directly affects your Attack and Defense stats, and comes with either physical or magical properties. Enchanting may fail and has a certain chance of damaging the item. Special items are required for the repair.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Enchanting, Dismantling, and Item Fusion&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;At the bottom of your Inventory window, you'll see the Forge, Dismantle, Infuse, and Crystal Fusion menus.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Forge: Enables you to enchant and upgrade items. You can also repair damaged items here.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Dismantle: Enables you to salvage materials from unwanted items. Bring the cursor over the item you want to dismantle to see the materials that it will yield when dismantled.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Infuse: Enables you to add options to items. Infusing items requires various fodder gear with multiple random options. Upon infusion, some of the random options on the fodder gear will be transferred to the target item. The number of item options you can add is determined by an item's available Infusion slots.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Crystal Fusion: You can fuse three crystals of the same class and rarity into a random new Crystal.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;There are seven types of Accessory items: Earrings, Rings, Circlets, Necklaces, Brooches, Belts, and Masks.&lt;BR&gt;Accessories provide you with special options that gear items can't. Accessories can be found in dungeons, and can be upgraded.&lt;BR&gt;Items with good options are highly valuable. Those without them are not, and can be easily obtained through the TradeBroker or other sources at fairly low prices.&lt;BR&gt;Rings/Earrings: You can equip two rings and two earrings at the same time, and you can further enhance them with crystals for additional options.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Crystals have a chance to be destroyed when you die.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Brooches: Equip a Brooch, then and add it to an item shortcut to use any active skill it has by pressing the hotkey.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Miscellaneous items come in three types: Inner Armor, Relics, and Halidoms.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Inner Armor: Can be obtained from the premium shop, or for example from the Ghillieglade instance. It also appears as a low probability dungeon drop.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Relics/Halidoms: Can be found as dungeon drops, quest rewards, and random rewards. Relics and Halidoms can be upgraded up to 5 times, by using other Relics and Halidoms of the same type.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Put away the note.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
</VillagerDialog>
