<VillagerDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/VillagerDialog VillagerDialog.xsd" id="207640" huntingZoneId="0" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/VillagerDialog">
    <Text id="1" endSocial="0">
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">Welcome, hero!&lt;BR&gt;.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The Valkyon Federation always tries its best to support its operatives, and has many benefits in store for you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Please keep up the good work.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;May the blessings of the goddess be upon you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;B&gt;&lt;font color = '#FF0000'&gt;This note has no effect on XP gains or quest progression, and you may destroy it after reading it.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/B&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Companions&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Pets and Partners are special, personal NPCs equipped with convenient features. They can loot items. gather resources, provide extra character storage, and even use potions on you when your HP or MP are low.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Pets&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Pets are the most basic type of companion. You can buy them from the TERA Store or by spending 10 Legacy Essences. Some pets have special abilities. Pets, while summoned, gain XP equivalent to the amount of energy they recover by being fed, and over time can advance up to Level 10.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Growth: You can "feed" unwanted items to pets to increase their XP.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Combine: You can combine pets into a different pet with a chance of getting a partner instead. This chance increases to 100% if the pets you’re using are Level 10.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Evolution: When a pet reaches Level 10, it can be evolved at the cost of Evolution Cores and Gold. Evolution has a chance to fail, and generates a random partner upon success.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;B&gt;&lt;font color = '#FF0000'&gt;Caution: Partners are powerful pets that have skills. Please note that pets lose all their abilities when combined.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/B&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Note: Pets with 0 Energy can't be summoned. To summon them, press the Feed button and use pet food in your inventory to feed them first. Partners do not consume pet food, but can receive presents through the Present menu.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Partners&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Partners are powerful companions with Bond and Gifted skills. There are Uncommon, Rare, and Superior partners, and the higher their grade, the better they perform.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Upgrade: You can upgrade a partner by consuming another partner. Upgrading partners increases their Fellowship(Fellowship is maxed at 50). Fellowship, which affects the power of Bond skills, increases upon promotion by between 3 to 6 levels depending on the consumed partner's rarity.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Transfer: You may transfer abilities from a pet or a partner to another companion by using Gold.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Bond Skill: Bond Skills temporarily increases your Power, Physical Amplification, or Magic Amplification, and can be added to a skill shortcut for use. Bond skills give greater benefits and last longer according to the partner's current Fellowship.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Gifted Skill: Gifted Skills are passive skills that can help you in activities or battles.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Partner Adventures&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Partners can go on adventures (depending on their rarity) to gather items. Your partners will bring back various gatherable and dungeon-exclusive items after a while, but you gain nothing from adventures that are canceled midway.&lt;BR&gt;You can end an adventure (and bring your partner home to use) with an Instant Adventure Completion Coupons. Coupons are found as rare dungeon drops, as event rewards, or can be purchased int he TERA Store.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You will recieve an Instant Adventure Completion Coupon as a reward for completing this tutorial. Please feel free to use it.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Put away the note.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
</VillagerDialog>
