<VillagerDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/VillagerDialog VillagerDialog.xsd" id="602041" huntingZoneId="0" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/VillagerDialog">
    <Text id="1" endSocial="0">
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">1.&lt;BR&gt;I got word that my father passed away.&lt;BR&gt;He was cremated, as he requested, and his ashes were spread on the river bank near Velika.&lt;BR&gt;Words cannot explain my grief but tears I do not have.&lt;BR&gt;You can only spare so little grief when you're in war...&lt;BR&gt;...&lt;BR&gt;...&lt;BR&gt;Now, it's just Hughlyn and I left to carry on the family.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">2.&lt;BR&gt;The Erstengra family may be wealthy, but that wealth was born of thievery and crime.&lt;BR&gt;Moreover, Lanec Erstengra once lost all his men during battle as a result of his foolish orders.&lt;BR&gt;I can't believe that man has become deputy commander!&lt;BR&gt;I'm aware that we're short on supplies, but this decision is difficult to bear.&lt;BR&gt;...&lt;BR&gt;...&lt;BR&gt;Hughlyn strongly disagreed with the ridiculous plan and was demoted to a scout party.&lt;BR&gt;Just like Seir, I'm worried about Hughlyn. But on the other hand, I must say I was satisfied.&lt;BR&gt;The Granwoods are respected over the land for their pride and honor, never backing down on authority.&lt;BR&gt;(Pages are torn out.)&lt;PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;Previous page.&lt;/PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close the memoir.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">First day of the search mission:&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I found the flag that Hughlyn's troops used.&lt;BR&gt;Judging by the crusted blood, they  passed through this area some time ago.&lt;BR&gt;Something doesn't feel right.&lt;BR&gt;(Illegible—the ink is smeared.)&lt;PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;Previous page.&lt;/PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close the memoir.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">Third day of the search mission:&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I found the adjutant's body.&lt;BR&gt;Someone—or something—must have pierced him from the back, with some kind of blade.&lt;BR&gt;The Argons don't use these kind of weapons...&lt;PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;Previous page.&lt;/PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;The next page is torn out.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close the memoir.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">Eighth day of the search mission:&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Hughlyn was...(illegible)&lt;PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;Previous page.&lt;/PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;The next page is torn out.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close the memoir.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">4.&lt;BR&gt;Erstengra received a court-martial.&lt;BR&gt;The badge that my brother was clutching in his dead hands suggests Erstengra is guilty.&lt;BR&gt;Of course, Erstengra will be accused of murdering an ally during battle.&lt;PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;Previous page.&lt;/PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;The next page is torn out.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close the memoir.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">5.&lt;BR&gt;Once Kaiator was recovered, Lanec was released. At the same time, I heard that the war was over.&lt;BR&gt;I got orders to pack up and return to Velika the next day.&lt;BR&gt;They said I would be promoted to Garrison Commander.&lt;BR&gt;Truth be told, the federation worried that the Erstengra family would withdraw their support. That's why the expedition was put to an end so suddenly. Not to mention that the purpose was clearly to transfer Lanec from the military court and into a civil court, to reduce his sentence.&lt;BR&gt;...&lt;BR&gt;...&lt;BR&gt;The queen was right.&lt;BR&gt;It was all for nothing.&lt;BR&gt;Hughlyn, and all the other men we lost...&lt;PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;Previous page.&lt;/PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;The next page is torn out.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close the memoir.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">6.&lt;BR&gt;(You can sense the rage from the handwriting.)&lt;BR&gt;This is the last day for the Erstengra family.&lt;BR&gt;10 years were just too long.&lt;BR&gt;Rumors about them searching for Lok's Spear must have closed the deal.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Elleon has his doubts, but he will uncover nothing.&lt;BR&gt;...the deal with the queen is still in effect.&lt;BR&gt;It's time to be the new god and purify the world.&lt;PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;Previous page.&lt;/PREVPAGEBUTTON&gt;&lt;CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close the memoir.&lt;/CLOSEPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
</VillagerDialog>
