<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
             xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd"
             id="1"
             huntingZoneId="8"
             voiceTypeId="0"
             xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="5"
              voiceTypeId="0">Mission Orders&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We have received new information about the Core.Report to Commander Fraya at Allemantheia Headquarters immediately.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;-Fraya</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">Fraya asked you to start the search for Akasha and the Core in Velika. After your arrival in Castanic, Elleon told you that the Gulas from the Hungry Caverns has joined forces with Akasha. Once you had defeated Gluorn, the leader of the Gulas, in the Hungry Caverns, you found out from him and from the trade ledgers with Akasha that they had all fled to Fyrmount.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3"
          huntingZoneId="518"
          prevId="1"
          villagerId="1001">
        <Page social="5"
              voiceTypeId="0">I'll get straight to the point. Akasha has left Southern Shara, and it's almost certain she took the Core with her. I put in a word with our colleagues in Velika, and High Priestess Ciebel thinks she's found Akasha already.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Let's go."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">Allemantheia cannot spare me in this state. You'll have to go alone. Use this teleportal scroll, then talk to Ciebel in Velika.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Please hurry. Every day without the Core brings Allemantheia closer to slipping into the sands.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4"
          huntingZoneId="63"
          prevId="3"
          villagerId="1167">
        <Page social="5"
              voiceTypeId="0">I was hoping Fraya would send you, &lt;PCNAME&gt;. I sensed two powerful presences—one emanating an elven serenity, the other seething with barely suppressed rage—enter the Hungry Caverns.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"And one is Akasha?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">Yes. The echoes are fading, but she can't have gone far.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Go to Castanica first. Elleon is there.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5"
          huntingZoneId="61"
          prevId="4"
          villagerId="1104">
        <Page social="5"
              voiceTypeId="0">&lt;PCNAME&gt;! Wherever I go, I hear of your exploits. We were blindsided in Allemantheia, but this time, we'll regain the Core.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"You know where it is?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="5"
              voiceTypeId="0">Ciebel gave me a few leads. You know how good her sources are!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Someone matching Akasha's description has been seen among the gulas. It's not much, but it's a lead.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;{@linkcreature:61#1105#Fraya} might have more details for you.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6"
          huntingZoneId="61"
          prevId="5"
          villagerId="1105">
        <Page social="5"
              voiceTypeId="0">Akasha is hiding among the gulas, and I'm not sure why. Why bring the Core here?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I have my own suspicions...suspicions that drew me here, even though I'm needed back home. Also, here is in the scope of Velika.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Regardless of my problems, we need the Core back. Check in with Smernav at the Gula Avenger Outpost. He'll get you inside the caverns.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7"
          huntingZoneId="208"
          prevId="6"
          villagerId="1002">
        <Page social="5"
              voiceTypeId="0">Elleon and Fraya sent you? Well, I hope you like a good fight. The gulas will give you all you can handle.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The most dangerous of them is the enforcer {@linkcreature:8#8021#Dulinka} and his mekkitar guards.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;They're in the innermost part of the first floor; take them out, and you may gain some advantage.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="8"
          huntingZoneId="208"
          prevId="7"
          villagerId="1015">
        <Page social="5"
              voiceTypeId="0">Don't hurt me! It's not my fault!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Sure, I kept a high elf prisoner, but I didn't eat him!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Look at me! I'm skin and bones! The high elf smelled so...so delicious. But I was a good gula. He still has all his fingers and toes!&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Where is he now?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">The high elf? Akasha has him, I bet.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;First I was supposed to move the elf along with the supplies, but then Akasha changed plans.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Now the orders say just move the supplies, not the tasty, juicy elf. My ledger says so!</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="9"
          huntingZoneId="208"
          prevId="8"
          villagerId="1041">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">You've got gluron's ledger!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I've heard that the gulas stocked in on a lot recently. I can't be sure, but it has to do something with Akasha.&lt;BR&gt;This place definitely has more than we know.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;First, let's go back to Fraya and check the ledger.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="10"
          huntingZoneId="208"
          prevId="8"
          villagerId="1041">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">Let's go!</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="11"
          huntingZoneId="61"
          prevId="9"
          villagerId="1105">
        <Page social="5"
              voiceTypeId="0">The ledger confirms what we thought—Akasha has kidnapped the Core, and she's taking him to Fyrmount.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
