<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" id="5" huntingZoneId="1" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">[Urgent Letter]&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Do you remember when the argons attacked Baldera? I have finally found out what they are up to.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;When you read this letter, please come to the ancient ruins at the Central Baldera Camp. It's urgent.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Hasmina</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">You read Hasmina's letter and met your companions at the Central Baldera Camp.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The argons have attacked Baldera again, and Shandra's root has spread to the Spring of Arun.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The root originates in Shandra's Nest. You found out that the argons want to use the power of the spring to resurrect Manahan. They also have a special plan to capture Baldera.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You have decided to take action against Manahan and the argons.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3" huntingZoneId="1" prevId="1" villagerId="31010">
        <Page social="0">Thank you for coming so quickly.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;As you know, the argons have attacked Baldera and are spreading.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I've learned that Dakuryon is aiding Manahan. As we expected, the argons have planted their vile root in the Spring of Arun.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Unfortunately, our soldiers were too weak to stop them.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4" huntingZoneId="1" prevId="3" villagerId="31020">
        <Page social="0">I could only stand by and watch them plant the root in the spring.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We haven't given up the fight yet, but the argons have captured the spring. The situation is tense.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;There is only one reason why the argons would use the power of the spring.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"To resurrect Manahan?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Precisely. That power is necessary to bring Manahan into this world.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I was unable to stop them, even though I knew their plan.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;My own weakness makes me angry. Just look at that greedy root...</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5" huntingZoneId="1" prevId="4" villagerId="31070">
        <Page social="0">Using the power of the spring isn't so easy.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Don't forget that my clan became addicted when trying to harness it. Without precise knowledge, it is extremely dangerous to try to control its power.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The argons still don't know how to use the power. You have to stop them.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6" huntingZoneId="1" prevId="5" villagerId="31011">
        <Page social="0">The Argon Priests are trying to use the spring. Take them out.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7" huntingZoneId="1" prevId="6" villagerId="31012">
        <Page social="0">Ahead of us are Red Argon Incubators.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;When argons evolve, they turn red. This evolution requires a lot of energy, however, so they are very rare. I've never seen so many incubators.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The argons must be trying to utilize the power of the spring. &lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Are they planning to evolve large numbers of argons?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">That seems the only logical answer. The argons are trying to bolster their army.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We need to get an overview of the situation.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="8" huntingZoneId="1" prevId="7" villagerId="31023">
        <Page social="0">The magisters are evolved argons. It's a bad sign for us that they're here.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Let's follow the root. If you own a flying mount, use it to get up there.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="9" huntingZoneId="1" prevId="8" villagerId="31014">
        <Page social="0">The root has spread toward Manaya's Core in Granarkus.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I remember the name... something Manaya...&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Do you mean Armen Manaya?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">That's right! Armen Manaya! He is Manahan's son.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The fact that the root leads to Manaya's Core and the situation in general suggest that the argons are following a plan for the capture of Baldera.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We must stop them. Let's head to the base and consider how to proceed.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
