<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
             xsi:schemaLocation="https://tera-arise.io/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd"
             id="3"
             huntingZoneId="506"
             voiceTypeId="0"
             xmlns="https://tera-arise.io/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">Laaran is looking for you.&lt;BR&gt;Speak with Laaran in Tria.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">To everyone's surprise but yours, the Stronghold of Blood was not a safe place at all. On your way to save the villagers, you and Elleon encountered an enormous castle in the sky. From out of this flying castle emerged hordes of the butterflies that you saw in Velik’s dream. They attacked the refugees' transports, forcing them out of the sky. You hurried to the crash site and rescued all the survivors you could find.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3"
          huntingZoneId="70"
          prevId="1"
          villagerId="1011">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">We've decided to send the villagers to the Stronghold of Blood until this plague has been dealt with.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The area outside is dangerous, but they should be safe behind the fortifications. Please gather them up and make sure they get to the transports.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I'm needed here to coordinate the evacuation, so they'll need someone they trust, and I can't think of anyone they'd trust more than you.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4"
          huntingZoneId="70"
          prevId="3"
          villagerId="1020">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">It's a good thing that I contacted Jordal beforehand.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We won't be back for a long time, right?&lt;BR&gt;I should take some food, fruit, and...yes, some pills for travel sickness. Long-sleeved clothing, and...</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5"
          huntingZoneId="70"
          prevId="3"
          villagerId="1039">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">These recruits have never seen any real action before. All they had were drills. I'm not sure if they'll do a good job guarding the villagers.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;But who knows? Maybe one of them is the next &lt;PCNAME&gt;...</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6"
          huntingZoneId="70"
          prevId="3"
          villagerId="1014">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">One hero can sometimes do what a hundred soldiers cannot.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;But when it comes to mundane, day-to-day bravery, it is soldiers who are the true heroes.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7"
          huntingZoneId="70"
          prevId="3"
          villagerId="1042">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">If we're going to the Stronghold of Blood, a flying transport would be the safest way.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Going to the ruins was impossible after the soldiers pulled out. So, on the bright side, I'm glad I can finally go and take a look for myself.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="8"
          huntingZoneId="70"
          prevId="4"
          villagerId="1011">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">It breaks my heart to evacuate the village like this.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I've struggled to keep Tria safe, and failed more than I succeeded. Now this?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Ah, well. It was never about me...it was always about them.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;PCNAME&gt;, please get the civilians aboard the transports.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="9"
          huntingZoneId="70"
          prevId="8"
          villagerId="1064">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">What will become of our home...?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="10"
          huntingZoneId="70"
          prevId="9"
          villagerId="1065">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">We will come back one day, right?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="11"
          huntingZoneId="70"
          prevId="10"
          villagerId="1066">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">My recruits are all accounted for.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="12"
          huntingZoneId="70"
          prevId="11"
          villagerId="1067">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">I'm actually looking forward to getting a closer look at the ruins!</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="13"
          huntingZoneId="70"
          prevId="12"
          villagerId="1063">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">The last of the villagers are aboard the transports.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="14"
          huntingZoneId="70"
          prevId="13"
          villagerId="1053">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">No! I was too late!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I got word from our scouts: The amber powder is coming from Stronghold of Blood! We must get word to the transports and get those people back here.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;If they land in the stronghold, they'll all be infected!</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="15"
          huntingZoneId="70"
          prevId="14"
          villagerId="1011">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">This is devastating... I've put everyone's lives in danger...&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We must go after the transports!&lt;BR&gt;They'll be flying past Serenity Valley... Hudere should be there. He can tell you if the transports have already passed by. Go! Now!&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"I'm on my way!"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">I can send you directly to the camp where Hudere is.&lt;BR&gt;Are you ready to go now?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="16"
          huntingZoneId="227"
          prevId="15"
          villagerId="1037">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">Luckily, the airship hasn't arrived at the fortress yet.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We'll the fort to make sure the people on the airship are safe.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;PCNAME&gt;, please get the villagers to safety.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="17"
          huntingZoneId="27"
          prevId="16"
          villagerId="1000">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">I came as soon as I heard you'd arrived.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The transports are nearly at the Stronghold of Blood.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We have to stop them before they set down!</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="18"
          huntingZoneId="27"
          prevId="17"
          villagerId="1014">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">There's no time to lose!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We have to get inside quickly and get those refugees out of there.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Elleon went on ahead, and he should have reached the stronghold by now. But that flying castle... those giant butterflies... he's going to need our help.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Go! I'm right behind you!"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">We should split up, search different crash sites.&lt;BR&gt;We need to work fast.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="19"
          huntingZoneId="27"
          prevId="18"
          villagerId="1001">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">Monsters...!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; Giant butterflies-everywhere!! They're spreading around some kind of amber-colored powder! The rest of my unit is still in there... if we don't hurry, they'll all get the crystal plague!</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="20"
          huntingZoneId="27"
          prevId="19"
          villagerId="1015">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">The transport just fell out of the sky...!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I got separated from my husband... I can't find him!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Please promise me you'll find him.&lt;BR&gt;I can't live without him!&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"I'll find him. Wait here."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">Thank you! Thank you so much!&lt;BR&gt;May the gods guide your way.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="21"
          huntingZoneId="27"
          prevId="20"
          villagerId="1016">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">Those... butterfly things surrounded the transport and... we crashed!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;People were screaming, crying... we all panicked and...&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"You're safe now."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">I don't know what happened. I... thank you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;There are still people inside. They're back that way... up the stairs, then to the left. Please save them!</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="22"
          huntingZoneId="27"
          prevId="21"
          villagerId="1017">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">The corpse is covered in blood and crystal powder.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="23"
          huntingZoneId="27"
          prevId="22"
          villagerId="1003">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">We found some survivors, but there are still too many unaccounted for.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The bulk of the wreckage is this way... on the other side of all these giant butterflies.&lt;BR&gt;I'll distract them... &lt;BR&gt;You go see if you can find any more survivors!&lt;BR&gt;If you find any, send them to me.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="24"
          huntingZoneId="27"
          villagerId="1018">
        <Page social="0">They seem to have lost all their strength. We should take them to Leander.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="25"
          huntingZoneId="27"
          prevId="23"
          villagerId="502">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">I'll get these survivors to the refugee camps. You should report to Seir, and let him know that the Stronghold of Blood isn't secure.&lt;BR&gt;Bringing these people here was the federation's idea in the first place. We obviously need a better plan now.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Jelena and I will go do some reconnaissance on tha... whatever it is in the sky.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Okay."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">I have a spare teleport scroll. When we're done here, I'll send you back to Liberation Station.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Check in with Velnen... see if he needs any more help here, then join us in Spring Valley.&lt;BR&gt;We'll fill you in on what we find out when you get there.&lt;BR&gt;I can teleport you when you're ready to go.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="26"
          huntingZoneId="227"
          prevId="25"
          villagerId="1008">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">Nice to see you still in one piece.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I should've known that the transports would crash...&lt;BR&gt;It feels like I dreamed about it, or something like it.&lt;BR&gt;Anyway... it looks like you've found all the survivors we're likely to find. Good work.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"I only wish we'd found more still alive."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">Get some rest.&lt;BR&gt;I'll take care of the survivors, but I might need you to help me, if you have the time.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
