<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" id="1" huntingZoneId="58" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1" huntingZoneId="58" prevId="0" villagerId="21008">
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">&lt;PCNAME&gt;! &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Have you heard of the Dungeon Resonance phenomenon in Baldera?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The Resonance has created gates connecting Arborea to countless dimensions. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Would you be interested in getting to the bottom of this phenomenon with me?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">You learned that the world shards containing the power of the core were the reason why Arborea had become connected to other dimensions. &lt;BR&gt;Obtain a Resonance Stone so that you can open the gate and defeat a level 1 boss.&lt;BR&gt;Continuously level up so that you can face the challenges of even higher levels.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3" huntingZoneId="58" prevId="1" villagerId="21008">
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">Isn't it amazing that there's a gate that connects Arborea with another dimension?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;How great must the effects of the destroyed core be for a phenomenon like this to happen?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"I'd be interested in that too."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">Good.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Here's a replica of a &lt;img src='img://__Icon_Items.resonanceStone_Tex' width='22' height='22' vspace='-6'/&gt;&lt;font color='#0000FF'&gt;Resonance Stone&lt;/font&gt;, &lt;PCNAME&gt;.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Take it to the &lt;font color='#0000FF'&gt;Bloody Resonance Gate&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Watch carefully what happens. &lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"What's a Resonance Stone?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">It works as a kind of key to open the &lt;font color='#0000FF'&gt;Resonance Gate&lt;/font&gt; and link Arborea to other dimensions.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;These stones are so important that even I don't have an original one. But I do have something very similar.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Shall we test what happens with it?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4" huntingZoneId="58" prevId="3" villagerId="21008">
        <Page social="0">Did you notice the reaction between the Resonance Gate and the replica Resonance Stone?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Unfortunately, the replica didn't generate the full response, but I did identify one thing.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;img src='img://__Icon_Items.resonanceStone_Tex' width='22' height='22' vspace='-6'/&gt;&lt;font color='#0000FF'&gt;One Resonance Stone&lt;/font&gt; isn't enough to open the gate.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"So, how can the gate be opened?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">You'll have to find allies who also possess a &lt;img src='img://__Icon_Items.resonanceStone_Tex' width='22' height='22' vspace='-6'/&gt;&lt;font color='#0000FF'&gt;Resonance Stone&lt;/font&gt;, and form a group of 5 players.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The group leader can select the difficulty at the &lt;font color='#0000FF'&gt;Resonance Gate&lt;/font&gt;, and if every group member agrees, you can enter the dungeon.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;No one knows what dungeon you'll end up in.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Where can I get a Resonance Stone?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">&lt;img src='img://__Icon_Items.resonanceStone_Tex' width='22' height='22' vspace='-6'/&gt;&lt;font color='#0000FF'&gt;Resonance Stones&lt;/font&gt; can be obtained in group dungeons. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Do you want to enter a &lt;font color='#0000FF'&gt;Resonance Dungeon&lt;/font&gt; now?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Like I said, you'll need to form a group of 5 players. Then you'll be able to enter the dungeon via the gate.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You should start with level 1.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Go though the &lt;font color='#0000FF'&gt;Bloody Gate&lt;/font&gt; and bring me the boss's item.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5" huntingZoneId="58" prevId="4" villagerId="21008">
        <Page social="0">I'm impressed that you completed the dungeon within the time limit.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;If you carry on diligently collecting &lt;img src='img://__Icon_Items.resonanceStone_Tex' width='22' height='22' vspace='-6'/&gt;&lt;font color='#0000FF'&gt;Resonance Stones&lt;/font&gt;, you'll be able to attempt even higher levels. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;There are, after all, an infinite number of dimensions.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6" huntingZoneId="58" prevId="4" villagerId="21008">
        <Page social="0">&lt;font color='#0000FF'&gt;FROZEN Otherworldly Shards&lt;/font&gt; can be obtained by completing the Resonance Dungeon (Hard) within the time limit.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Enter the Resonance Dungeon via the &lt;font color='#0000FF'&gt;Bloody Resonance Gate&lt;/font&gt;.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
