<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" id="4" huntingZoneId="213" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0" />
    <Text id="100" huntingZoneId="13" prevId="0" villagerId="8008">
        <Page social="0" />
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" huntingZoneId="13" prevId="0" villagerId="8008">
        <Page social="4">I'll talk to my sentries, to see if any of them can confirm any of this information.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;As long as you're here, &lt;PCNAME&gt;, you should head up to the World Tree, and see if you can find anything up there that might point to who's responsible for this atrocity. I think Magister Jovin's up there; check in with him.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Okay."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3" huntingZoneId="13" prevId="2" villagerId="8009">
        <Page social="4">Oh, &lt;PCNAME&gt;. I've heard... I mean... Your reputation proceeds you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I'm glad you're here to help. The immediate danger has passed, but we still don't know what happened here—and with any luck, the World Tree is not a complete loss.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The Armillariscope should determine if there's any hope for the tree. &lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"How does it work?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4">This tree is a relic of the creation of the Dream—it sprang from a tear shed by a grieving goddess. According to legend, there are many such trees scattered throughout the world, though this is the only one I've ever seen.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;What made this tree special is that it still retains some divine essence, which is why the federation originally came to the Island of Dawn. But in the years since we discovered it, we haven't been able to determine what that divine power does...let alone how to utilize it.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Now it seems like we might never get that chance. The Armillariscope should be able to tell us if there's any hope.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;In fact, if you'd be so kind as to activate the device, we can begin our examination.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Very well."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4" huntingZoneId="13" prevId="3" villagerId="8009">
        <Page social="4">Hm. That's...not promising.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;There is still some divine essence in the tree...but it is barely registering on the Armillariscope. Disturbing, to say the least, given that when I first took readings three years ago, the divine essence nearly melted the scope.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Unless we find a way to restore the divine energy—which is unlikely—the World Tree will die...and the Island of Dawn along with it.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"What will it take to restore the tree's energy?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4">I honestly do not know. I have never encountered a situation like this.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I suppose it would help if we could determine who is responsible for this damage. If that person knows how it was done, they might know how to undo it.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"If I identify the culprit, you'll be the first person I notify."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5" huntingZoneId="13" prevId="4" villagerId="8010">
        <Page social="4">This is very curious. At first blush, these soldiers were crushed to death by falling debris.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;But they were dead before the debris began falling. See there? Their throats were cut. The killer must have crept up on them, one at a time...or perhaps several killers, working in concert, did this terrible deed.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The method would suggest a professional killer...or perhaps a cadre of skilled assassins.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Could someone like that be on the island?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4">It is extremely unlikely. One or two, yes. An entire group of assassins, no. The island is only so big. Such a group, traveling in numbers, would draw attention.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;No, I suspect that we are dealing with one assassin, quite skilled, traveling incognito...perhaps disguised as a visitor to the island. And at the moment, we have a number of those...but it seems unlikely that this assassin would be hiding among the alliance delegations. They are all small groups, who know each other. It must be someone operating completely alone.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"One killer, working alone. Got it. Thanks."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6" huntingZoneId="13" prevId="5" villagerId="8011">
        <Page social="4">We were on duty when all of this happened...stationed at the Middle Island Camp. So many of our friends died during this disaster!&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Did you happen to notice the Iron Order in the area, at the time?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4">The Iron Order?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;No, it was a quiet night. No one coming or going. Why?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Seems I was misinformed. Thank you."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7" huntingZoneId="13" prevId="6" villagerId="8012">
        <Page social="4">(The body is a dead federation soldier. He appears to have died after being stabbed twice in the chest.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;His sword is still in its scabbard, but he's clutching something tightly in his hand.)&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Examine what's in the dead soldier's hand.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4">(In his hand there is a single earring.)&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"This...looks familiar."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="8" huntingZoneId="13" prevId="7" villagerId="8013">
        <Page social="4">I can't prove any of this, but I think I know who killed all of these people.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"I'm listening."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4">There was a guy who came to the island a few days before all of these alliance groups showed up. I was at the dock when he arrived, and I heard him say he was a treasure hunter. I remember, because it was kind of odd. I mean, everything of value here has long since been discovered, collected, and sent to Velika.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;But here's the suspicious thing: He's only really been interested in the tree. And talking to people.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Talking to people? Who was he talking to?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4">Guards, the banker...hmm. Who else?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Oh, right: Jorah? Jorva? The magister of the Enlightened Union. Oh, and Aknam, too, the leader of the Iron Order group.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"What did this treasure hunter look like?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4">Dark clothes, twin swords. Earrings.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I know it's vague, but I've seen him on the island several times since all this happened, so I know he's still around.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"I think I know this man. Thanks. I'll keep an eye out for him."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="9" huntingZoneId="13" prevId="8" villagerId="8008">
        <Page social="4">A man in black? The treasure hunter?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;He's been tracking down and bringing back the dead and wounded ever since this happens. Why would he...?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Although...that would be perfect cover for someone who needed to come and go a lot...and maybe the bodies he's bringing back aren't dead when he finds them...&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;See if you can find him, &lt;PCNAME&gt;. I think I would very much like to talk to him as soon as possible.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"You can count on me."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
