<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
             xsi:schemaLocation="https://tera-arise.io/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd"
             id="77"
             huntingZoneId="183"
             voiceTypeId="0"
             xmlns="https://tera-arise.io/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">[Dougal's Letter]&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Greetings, &lt;PCNAME&gt;!&lt;BR&gt;After hearing many stories of your heroism, I could not wait to write this letter.&lt;BR&gt;I know just the place for heroes like you.&lt;BR&gt;Find me at Highwatch, if you're interested.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">Dougal explained about Fraywind Canyon.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3"
          huntingZoneId="183"
          prevId="1"
          villagerId="1021">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">There are no doubts about your skill and courage. &lt;BR&gt;I believe you are qualified.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Arborea's bravest have gathered to renovate an abandoned arena... a little haven for showing off their skills.&lt;BR&gt;Don't bother thinking about fighting against your own federation allies.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;It's a privilege not many people get to experience... a chance to demonstrate your prowess. &lt;b&gt;Fraywind Canyon&lt;/b&gt; is the place to exercise that privilege... a place for competing against other brave soldiers!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Doesn't your heart start to pound at the thought?&lt;BR&gt;Are you willing to give it a try?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4"
          huntingZoneId="183"
          prevId="3"
          villagerId="1021">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">I knew you'd enjoy it!&lt;BR&gt;Any champion craving power would not pass up an opportunity like this.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;But Fraywind Canyon is filled with passionate warriors, so the battles fought there are contested with great intensity. You should prepare well before you enter.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Take this book with you. Consider it a welcome gift. Study it well. I'm sure it will be a great help for you in this and many other arenas.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
