<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" id="2" huntingZoneId="172" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1" huntingZoneId="63" prevId="0" villagerId="1534">
        <Page social="4">Thanks to your help we were able to fix the wheel and deliver the promised goods in time. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You really can be counted on. I have one last thing to ask of you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I am begging you.&lt;BR&gt;My good name is on the line. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I'd be eternally grateful if you could take care of it for me.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"What is it?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">This box contains a part made by a ingenious engineer. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;It is beyond comparison with any other goods. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Please bring this box to Tamari.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">After entering the sky cruiser you meet the cute Popori Paesyn, and Mari tells you everything about the expedition to the Lost Continent.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3" huntingZoneId="63" prevId="1" villagerId="1533">
        <Page social="0">Tonas came through? I wondered if he'd swindled me.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Very well. I know who you are. You're cleared to ascend to the dock.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4" huntingZoneId="63" prevId="3" villagerId="1502">
        <Page social="4">Oh, I'm so clumsy!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Well, hello!&lt;BR&gt;My nose is never wrong. You smell like a nice person, so I like you. Do &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; like me?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Hey, can I ask you a favor? This wind tore some really important secret papers from my bag. I have to get them back!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Will you help me?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5" huntingZoneId="63" prevId="4" villagerId="1502">
        <Page social="4">My hero! It would have been a disaster if those pages had been found by the enemy...or her.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;PCNAME&gt;, are you boarding the sky cruiser, too?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Indeed."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">That's great! You're great. We'll adventure together!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You should report to Rafe! See you in the sky!</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6" huntingZoneId="63" villagerId="1502">
        <Page social="0">Where are the rest of the pages?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7" huntingZoneId="63" prevId="5" villagerId="1503">
        <Page social="4">You're the last soldier on the list. Good!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Please deliver the manifest to Maribel. Oh, and thanks to you the supplies will be loaded soon.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="8" huntingZoneId="63" prevId="7" villagerId="1566">
        <Page social="4">Excellent work. Good luck on your mission.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
