<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" id="3" huntingZoneId="1" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">You have found the Spring of Arun and arrived in Balderon.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Ask the inhabitants of Balderon about the argons while Hasmina reports to Kaia about the spring.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">You have found the Spring of Arun and arrived in Balderon.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;For a long time, it was believed that the ancient city of Balderon had been destroyed in a forgotten war, but in fact it is untouched and is as resplendent as ever. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Additionally, there is a connection to another dimension here.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3" huntingZoneId="1" prevId="1" villagerId="11000">
        <Page social="0">Your reputation precedes you, &lt;PCNAME&gt;. It's a pleasure to meet you in Balderon.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;No one knows why the barrier disappeared. But as it has only just happened, many people still don't know that you can live here. But soon more will come and Balderon will be transformed into a big city.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"What do you know about the argons?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Argons? Hmm... I didn't know that they'd appeared around here. But perhaps I'm not the best source for rumors.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Why don't you ask the Fishing Trader? He's friendly and always well-informed.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4" huntingZoneId="58" prevId="3" villagerId="10092">
        <Page social="0">Have I heard any rumors about sightings of argons near Balderon?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;And here I was, thinking you'd come here to buy bait...&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;So, is the rumor true? It seems like argons have been sighted again. I'm sure the Pegasus Steward must have seen their movements from a Pegasus.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5" huntingZoneId="58" prevId="4" villagerId="10170">
        <Page social="0">Have I ever seen argons?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Of course I have! The first time I saw them was near the entrance to Baldera. Recently, I've spotted them near the spring. Haven't you seen any?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;That may well be the case. They're not always around. Sometimes they turn up briefly, then disappear again. They don't seem to pose much of a threat right now, but then they are still Argon, aren't they?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;They will never change. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Have you ever heard of the Resonance Gate? &lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Resonance Gate?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Most visitors to Balderon come here because they've heard of the Resonance Gate. I'm surprised you don't know what it is.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;In Baldera there's a way to connect this dimension with other dimensions. This phenomenon is called "Dungeon Resonance". The Resonance Gate allows you to enter dungeons in other dimensions. You can see it if you go to the end of the bridge. You can't miss it.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6" huntingZoneId="1" prevId="5" villagerId="10005">
        <Page social="0">&lt;PCNAME&gt;! So, you've heard about Dungeon Resonance too. &lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Did you report to Kaia?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Yes. Kaia had sensed this new energy, but she wasn't able to attribute it to the Spring of Arun. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The energy has grown much weaker recently. She was delighted at the news of the discovery of the Spring of Arun. Of course, she was distressed about the contamination of the spring, but she firmly believed that the spring could be cleansed again.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Can you tell me what this is? This Resonance Gate?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7" huntingZoneId="1" prevId="6" villagerId="10205">
        <Page social="0">*cough* I've figured it out! I knew it, I'm amazing!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;By analyzing the wavelength of the Resonance Gate, I found similarities between it and the amplitude of Exodor. If I connect this median line with the peak value... and you look at this line and the value of the tangent of the circle... &lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"I have no idea what you're talking about."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Tsk, tsk, dummy.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Simply put, this means that the Resonance Gate was created by the destruction of the core in Exodor. The energy that was released combined with the fragments of the Veil.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;It's an unusual phenomenon that connects other dimensions to Balderon. The Spring of Arun alone had already piqued my interest, but the existence of Resonance Gates is really impressive. Hahaha. *cough* *cough*</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
