<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
             xsi:schemaLocation="https://tera-arise.io/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd"
             id="1"
             huntingZoneId="3107"
             voiceTypeId="0"
             xmlns="https://tera-arise.io/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">[Urgent Letter]&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;PCNAME&gt;!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Do you remember how the argons kept appearing in Baldera from time to time?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;They would suddenly appear and then just disappear again. I have finally been able to find out what they're up to.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Please come to Balderon as quickly as possible. I could really use your help.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">You met an injured soldier who had been attacked by argons. He told you that the Shurians' territory was slowly being argonized. You then departed for the argon-occupied territory.&lt;BR&gt;There you saw that plants and Shurian warriors had been argonized.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The argons have set up an argon teleportal and are using it to teleport argons to Balderon. You watched the Argon Priests did Dakuryon's bidding, who had adopted Manahan's voice</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3"
          huntingZoneId="1"
          prevId="1"
          villagerId="10012">
        <Page social="0">Do you remember how the argons kept appearing in Baldera from time to time?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;They would suddenly appear and then just disappear again. I have finally been able to find out what they're up to.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;They want to argonize Baldera.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;They launched a surprise attack, injuring many of our soldiers, and some of them even died.&lt;BR&gt;We must question the surviving soldiers and use the information to stop the argons.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You'll help us, won't you?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4"
          huntingZoneId="1"
          prevId="3"
          villagerId="30060">
        <Page social="0">The argons suddenly appeared, and we thought they would disappear again as they always do.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;So we left down our guard. That should never have been allowed to happen...&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The argons have captured the Shurians' territory, and they must have argonized it all by now.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5"
          huntingZoneId="1"
          prevId="4"
          villagerId="30001">
        <Page social="0">Oh no! Those giant Shurians have been argonized too.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Do they really intend to argonize all life in Arborea?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6"
          huntingZoneId="1"
          prevId="5"
          villagerId="30070">
        <Page social="0">How sad...&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;My friends were once poisoned and lived like monsters. And now they've been argonized too and will forever be tormented by pain.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Please help them find eternal rest.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I'm begging you...</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7"
          huntingZoneId="1"
          prevId="6"
          villagerId="30000">
        <Page social="0">Is that an argon transport plane?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;They must have used it to get here.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Wait... There's a teleportal over there that wasn't there before. Let's see where it leads to.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="8"
          huntingZoneId="1"
          prevId="7"
          villagerId="30003">
        <Page social="0">Where has Dakuryon gone with the Argon Magister?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Why has he joined forces with the argons? I have to find out what he's up to.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
