<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
             xsi:schemaLocation="https://tera-arise.io/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd"
             id="11"
             huntingZoneId="172"
             voiceTypeId="0"
             xmlns="https://tera-arise.io/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1"
          huntingZoneId="172"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="1006">
        <Page social="4">The guwangis are the native inhabitants of the Savage Reach. They are a barbaric race, and they even eat human flesh. Madat being kidnapped by them is a real problem. &lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"You can count on me."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Really? Thank you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Having seen what short work you made of the Manticore, I have no doubt that you won't have a problem with the guwangis either.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Go on ahead and find Madat. I will follow you soon with the others.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">You save Magistrate Madat, helped the Khirians, and reached their sanctuary.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3"
          huntingZoneId="172"
          prevId="1"
          villagerId="1012">
        <Page social="4">"The rise of one star means another must set… I am more than happy to go as this new star will change everything. Mjusu Kraal."</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4"
          huntingZoneId="172"
          prevId="3"
          villagerId="1013">
        <Page social="0">(Something is carved under the lid: Madat.)</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5"
          huntingZoneId="172"
          prevId="4"
          villagerId="1014">
        <Page social="0">No, please! Please don't kill me!&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Did you see an old man in a funny hat?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Yes. Yes! The hat with long ears. I saw him not long ago.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;If he's strong enough, the guwangis will enslave him. If not, well, they'll eat anything.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6"
          huntingZoneId="172"
          prevId="5"
          villagerId="1107">
        <Page social="0">What took so long? Destiny isn't what it used to be.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Let's get out of here!</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7"
          huntingZoneId="172"
          prevId="6"
          villagerId="1106">
        <Page social="0">Well done, southerner. Perhaps I was rash to judge you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The Khirians have a hideout in the cave up the hill behind me.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Meet me there. The guwangis will want revenge for today.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="8"
          huntingZoneId="172"
          prevId="7"
          villagerId="1206">
        <Page social="4">Welcome to our refuge.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;This place is not like home, but it's safe enough. Your forces may join us through the teleportal and your wounded may recover here.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
