<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" id="1" huntingZoneId="84" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">An urgent message from Tamur reaches you. Go to Kaiator and meet Tamur there.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">Tamur asks you for help as unexpected events are occurring in Granarkus. Tamur asks you to go meet Hazel in Granarkus to find out the cause of the various phenomena.&lt;BR&gt;While you are investigating a glowing pipe near the Sorgalur Complex, Jelena turns up. When you are talking to Jelena, the earth suddenly starts to quake.&lt;BR&gt;Jelena is certain that the Hall of the Argon Queen is active. This matter needs to be reported to Seir so the Federation can respond to it.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3" huntingZoneId="528" prevId="1" villagerId="5005">
        <Page social="0">It's been a while, &lt;PCNAME&gt;.&lt;BR&gt;You probably know that the argons are up to their old tricks again, even though Shandra Manaya is dead, right?&lt;BR&gt;This is very alarming.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"What has happened?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">I received a message that a strange omen had appeared in Granarkus.&lt;BR&gt;I cannot say exactly what it is. However, it is clear that various phenomena have occurred.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We would like to help, but as you know, peace has still not returned to Kaiator.&lt;BR&gt;Please go to Granarkus and help the scholars there.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4" huntingZoneId="250" prevId="3" villagerId="1021">
        <Page social="0">Finally, help has arrived.&lt;BR&gt;And it's the guardian of Arborea, &lt;PCNAME&gt;, at that! Finally, I can breathe easily.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I was very worried because there was no apparent cause for the various incidents. &lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"What's going on?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Several things have happened.&lt;BR&gt;First of all, there are the argons' movements. However, far more important is the fact that the energy pipes that were inactive have started to radiate a strange light. The pipes shouldn't actually be glowing because Shandra Manaya is dead...&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The light that is glowing from the Sorgalur Complex to the Hall of the Argon Queen worries me the most. Please find out the cause of these occurrences. &lt;BR&gt;I fear we are on the brink of another argon war.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5" huntingZoneId="50" prevId="4" villagerId="1034">
        <Page social="0">You also seem to have figured out that something's going on here. &lt;BR&gt;I've come to investigate as Leander said that strange things were going on here.&lt;BR&gt;He said it could develop into serious danger.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Leander said that?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">I can understand why you would pull such a face. But please do not be too hasty with your judgment.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;It is undisputed that Leander made major mistakes in the past. However, a lot has changed since Elleon died.&lt;BR&gt;He seems to have taken over Elleon's role, and he does a lot of things for the common good.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Leander has also helped me. I felt so listless after Elleon's death.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6" huntingZoneId="50" prevId="5" villagerId="1034">
        <Page social="0">Oh my goodness! That was a big quake!&lt;BR&gt;The glowing pipe made me suspect it must be something serious, but now I'm sure that the Hall of the Argon Queen is active again. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You must leave for Velika immediately and report the occurrence to Commander Seir, &lt;PCNAME&gt;!&lt;BR&gt;We cannot handle the matter without the Federation's help.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
