<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" id="3" huntingZoneId="213" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0" />
    <Text id="100" huntingZoneId="13" prevId="0" villagerId="8003">
        <Page social="0" />
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" huntingZoneId="13" prevId="0" villagerId="8003">
        <Page social="4">At least that guy is helping.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;There are groups from each of the alliances out there, on training maneuvers. And they haven't lifted a finger to help. It's disgusting.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Still, if you're going out there, and you need a place to rest and recover, they have camps scattered around the island. Just don't expect them to come rescue you, if you get in trouble.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Anyway...good luck, &lt;PCNAME&gt;. And thanks for helping. It means a lot.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3" huntingZoneId="13" prevId="2" villagerId="8005">
        <Page social="4">Another federation flunky? By all means, let me put this time-wasting conversation on hold so I can have an equally pointless discussion with you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Well? What is it?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Have you been able to find any survivors?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4">Look. As I was telling this guy, we're really sorry that this disaster happened while we were here...but rescue operations just aren't in our budget.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We'll finish up our training exercises, and then get out of your hair, but we can't spare any troops or supplies to do the federation's job.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Now, if you have any more questions, come see me when I'm back in my office outside Velika. Good day.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Sorry to have taken your valuable time."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4" huntingZoneId="13" prevId="3" villagerId="8006">
        <Page social="4">Greetings, friend.&lt;BR&gt;I'm happy to report that the Enlightened Union has been actively seeking missing federation personnel...sadly, with little success thus far.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Please inform Adria that I will be taking my fellow agents out again shortly for another sweep of the area, in hopes of finding survivors.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Now, was there something else I could help you with?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Hm. What areas have you searched so far?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4">Alas, only a few, most in the immediate vicinity of this camp.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;It's the monsters, you see. We weren't expecting to have to deal with them, so we are ill-equipped to drive them off.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Pity. If they weren't so omnipresent, we might be able to search a larger area...&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"If I deal with them, can you step up your search?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4">That would be most...acceptable.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Very well, friend. You hurl yourself into mortal combat with these beasts, and should you prevail, I promise not only to increase the range of our search, but I will use the time to prepare a full report on our findings so far.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Very well. I'll be back shortly."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5" huntingZoneId="13" prevId="4" villagerId="8006">
        <Page social="4">You survived a battle with five of those beasts? My, my...you really are noteworthy, aren't you? I won't underestimate you next time. We can be absolutely certain of that.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"That's...fine. You had a report for me?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4">Ah, yes.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I thought it might interest you that the night of the World Tree's destruction, the Enlightened Union was conducting exercises near the Shrine of Yurian—from which one has a very clear view of the Tower Base.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;When the sky got dark, and the rumbling noises commenced, we were naturally curious. From our vantage point, I was able to clearly discern several individuals in Iron Order livery running away from the base in some haste.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I'm certainly not...suggesting their involvement. However, it seems likely that, given their proximity to the initial destruction, they may have a better idea of where to look for the federation's missing personnel.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Interesting. I'll look into that."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6" huntingZoneId="13" prevId="5" villagerId="8007">
        <Page social="4">What is it? It's bad enough our training exercise has been completely disrupted, but now you expect me to report on it?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Fine! Here's my official report: The Iron Order is officially annoyed! Got it? Want me to sign that for you?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"I'm told you were present when the World Tree was destroyed."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4">Hah! Wrong! Some investigator you are!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I was at Arun Heights. So were all my troops.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We passed through the camp down by Tainted Gorge. Why don't you go ask them, if you don't believe me?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Someone said they saw you by Tower Base."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4">Earlier in the day, yes! And we rushed back to help when the tree caught on fire. But between then? No!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Either somebody lied to you, or they're as blind as you are!&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Maybe I'll ask around Tainted Gorge, then."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4">Do that. Or go back and make sure your source is reliable.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Either way, you and your ridiculous accusations are not welcome here. Get out of my sight!&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Thanks. I'll be sure to mention that in my report."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7" huntingZoneId="13" prevId="6" villagerId="8008">
        <Page social="4">Hm. Seems like everybody has an excuse for not helping...from not enough resources to just being surly.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Jorivah's story is new, though. Interesting that he didn't think to share that...until after you came back alive from fighting those monsters.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We still need something solid to go on, &lt;PCNAME&gt;.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"I'll keep asking around, Adria."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
