<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
             xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd"
             id="20"
             huntingZoneId="1"
             voiceTypeId="0"
             xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">&lt;PCNAME&gt;.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The Federation has an urgent mission for you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I'd like you to carry out the mission.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You can find me in Balderon.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">The Federation sent Vella to track down Dakuryon's location, but she has since disappeared. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;When you went looking, you found Vella unconscious in Frost Reach. You brought her back to Allemantheia for her to regain her strength.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3"
          huntingZoneId="1"
          prevId="1"
          villagerId="10012">
        <Page social="0">The Federation has been trying to track down Dakuryon ever since the Argons started getting up to their old tricks again. The Federation is also searching for a man named Armen, whom Manahan had spoken about.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;However, contact with the High Elf Agent Vella has been lost. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You have been tasked with finding her. Let's look for Vella together.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Do you have any clues as to her whereabouts yet?&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">The last contact with her was in &lt;font color='#0000FF'&gt;Frost Reach&lt;/font&gt; in &lt;font color='#0000FF'&gt;Westonia&lt;/font&gt;. It's best if we start our search there.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4"
          huntingZoneId="234"
          prevId="3"
          villagerId="1001">
        <Page social="0">An elf by the name of Vella... &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Ah! I remember her. She looked very serious. That's why I noticed her in the first place. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;She'd asked if I'd encountered argons in this area, then set off toward the Azurice Shrine.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I'd warned her it was dangerous there, but to no avail.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"How can I find her?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">If you just keep marching on, you'll freeze to death in this place.&lt;BR&gt;I will loan you an excellent sleuth. Take him with you on your search.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Tukgu! Tukgu! Where did Tukgu go?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;This is such a hassle. He seems to be out of earshot.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Try cooking something to eat in the pot. He won't be able to resist the aroma, and he'll appear in a flash.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;He has a unique nose for tracking. Join him on the search.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5"
          huntingZoneId="34"
          prevId="4"
          villagerId="30400">
        <Page social="0">*woof* *pant*... *woof*</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6"
          huntingZoneId="34"
          prevId="4"
          villagerId="30500">
        <Page social="0">Urgh...&lt;BR&gt;The teleportal... I need the teleportal...&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;(She seems to have lost consciousness).</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7"
          huntingZoneId="34"
          prevId="6"
          villagerId="30000">
        <Page social="0">It's a stroke of luck that you found Vella, but her body temperature is low, so she's still in danger. Also, a strange glyph was found on her body. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Apparently it's something to do with a teleportal, but I think she's talking about the fragments&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Let's collect the fragments and go to Allemantheia. Vella needs treatment as soon as possible.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="8"
          huntingZoneId="34"
          prevId="7"
          villagerId="30200">
        <Page social="0">The teleportal has been smashed.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Let's collect the pieces and get ready for the journey to Allemantheia.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="9"
          huntingZoneId="34"
          prevId="8"
          villagerId="30100">
        <Page social="0">It's not looking good for Vella.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I'll take care of her. Please transport the teleportal.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="10"
          huntingZoneId="72"
          prevId="9"
          villagerId="40300">
        <Page social="0">I'll find someone who can look after Vella in her condition.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Please wait here with Hasmina.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
