<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" id="6" huntingZoneId="182" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1" huntingZoneId="182" prevId="0" villagerId="2032">
        <Page social="1" voiceTypeId="0">(She looks at the broken lucky charm.)&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;If this is an archdevan pendant, it must be valuable...&lt;BR&gt;Damn! Anyone who breaks something so valuable must be a complete idiot. There's no doubt about that.&lt;BR&gt;I wonder if there's a way to repair it... Of course there is.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;If I, Keezar, weren't so brilliant, those abominable archdevas wouldn't have locked me up and performed tests on me, would they?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I'll give it a try!&lt;BR&gt;I made a mistake. Sleep well, my dear archdeva, while I carry out my tests, hehe! &lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Come to you senses!"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="1" voiceTypeId="0">Huh? What was the last thing I said?&lt;BR&gt;Ah yes. You want me to repair this? &lt;BR&gt;What do I need for that...?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;That's right! I need that! What's it called again?&lt;BR&gt;That's it, the horn of an archdeva. Bring me that.&lt;BR&gt;I need... no... you need it.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Okay."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">Keezar, the greatest Khirian genius, didn't seem to be in her right mind.&lt;BR&gt;However, she was the only hope so you have no choice other than to trust in her abilities.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3" huntingZoneId="182" prevId="1" villagerId="2032">
        <Page social="1" voiceTypeId="0">Pretty, pretty horns! "A pointed projection of skin on the head of various animals consisting of a covering of keratin and other proteins surrounding a core of live bone." Ha! Bet you're wondering how I knew that, aren't you?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Is everyone here crazy?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4" huntingZoneId="182" villagerId="2032">
        <Page social="0">One horn, two horn, red horn, war-torn.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Not enough, my foreign friend!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Two horn, once worn! More horn, less scorn!</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5" huntingZoneId="182" prevId="3" villagerId="2032">
        <Page social="1" voiceTypeId="0">No need to get snippy, &lt;PCNAME&gt;. I have waited years in this awful place just to help you on your quest! But now that you're here, we can both go.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Let's talk outside, shall we?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"How do I get you out of here?" &lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="1" voiceTypeId="0">Click, click, double-quick! That's the wrong question! The right question is how do I get you out of here, when you're so slow?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"What? I'm not slow..."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6" huntingZoneId="182" prevId="5" villagerId="2036">
        <Page social="1" voiceTypeId="0">How did you find me so soon? I won't go back! You can't make me!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Wait...oh, you're still the same one. What was your name? What was your quest? Have I already asked you about your favorite color?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"I need this pendant repaired. Remember?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="1" voiceTypeId="0">A broken control pendant? How did you break this? They're meant to be indestructible and idiot-proof!&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"We've already had this conversation!"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="1" voiceTypeId="0">I cannot teach this one. No patience.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Fine. Glue you want. Glue you shall have.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Finally!"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
