<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" id="2" huntingZoneId="213" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0" />
    <Text id="100" huntingZoneId="13" prevId="0" villagerId="8001">
        <Page social="0" />
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" huntingZoneId="13" prevId="0" villagerId="8001">
        <Page social="4">There is simply no way that explosion was an accident.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Someone had to have destroyed the tree intentionally. We just don't know who...or why.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;For now, I'm investigating, and while I can't prove anything yet, I have a good idea what happened...&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Tell me."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4">I was inspecting the Tainted Gorge Outpost when the ground started shaking. When I looked up, I could see flames spreading rapidly up the trunk of the World Tree.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I rushed back to Tower Base, but by the time I got there, the camp was on fire. There was nothing we could do but evacuate.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Magister Jovin was one of the last people out. He stayed to see if there was anything we could do to help the tree. He said...hm.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We shouldn't talk here. Follow me.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Okay..."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3" huntingZoneId="13" prevId="2" villagerId="8002">
        <Page social="4">I don't know who set the fire that destroyed the World Tree...so I don't know who might be listening to us at the dock.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Some of the bodies coming back from Tower Base didn't die in the fire. Their throats were cut...and it's no coincidence that most of them were sentries, posted around the base of the tree.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Ordinarily, I'd suspect argons, or maybe archdevans...but we haven't seen any sign of either on the island.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Except...delegations from three alliances have recently arrived. They all gave more or less the same reason for being here—&amp;quot;training&amp;quot;—but they're behaving suspiciously.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Suspiciously? Like what?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4">Their "training" seems to consist of hurrying to some isolated spot at odd hours, then returning to their camps.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;And there have been a few clashes between them, when they cross paths. Nothing we couldn't handle, but the animosity is palpable.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;And starting a few days ago, they all started taking a special interest in the World Tree. The timing of that alone is suspicious.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"You think they caused this destruction?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4">It's too much of a coincidence...and a "coincidence" isn't enough to act on.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;But assuming it was them...why are they still here? If the goal was to destroy the tree, they succeeded. Why stick around?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;There has to be something else going on...something less obvious. I just don't know what it could be—which is why I wanted you to come here, and ask around. They don't know you; they'll be less on their guard.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"I'll check it out, and let you know what I find."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4" huntingZoneId="13" prevId="3" villagerId="8003">
        <Page social="4">&lt;PCNAME&gt;...&lt;PCNAME&gt;...&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I met someone by that name once...was that you?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;It was! The last time I saw you, you were a raw recruit! Just another "keener" stepping off the pegasus platform, looking lost and uncertain. Now look at you!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You've done well for yourself! What brings you back here...I mean, aside from the obvious?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"I heard what happened to the World Tree."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Yeah...yeah. It was bad. We lost a lot of people, and nobody seems to know why. Adria has barely slept, and Leander is acting weird...well, weirder than usual. We keep finding more bodies. And the whole island is infested with monsters again, big ones—like Bamarama that never ends.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Everybody's on edge.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You sure you want to go out there?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5" huntingZoneId="13" prevId="4" villagerId="8004">
        <Page social="4">If you're not crossing, then get out of the way for those of us who are!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;There are people dying out there while you two stand here wagging your tongues!&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Oh...I didn't realize you couldn't get past."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6" huntingZoneId="13" prevId="5" villagerId="8003">
        <Page social="4">Like I said: Everybody's on edge.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I guess I understand, though; that guy has been working day and night, finding the dead and injured and carrying them back across the bridge.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Who is he?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4">No idea...but he's clearly tough as nails. Did you notice he was bleeding, on the side of his head? He must've tangled with one of those big monsters...but he still keeps going out there.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I wish we had a dozen more just like him.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"I suppose so."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
