<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" id="1" huntingZoneId="3205" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">The Valkyon Federation is monitoring the draakons' movements in Exodor.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;They have been behaving strangely lately, which is why we need your help, &lt;PCNAME&gt;.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Could you come meet me at the base?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">After finding orbless draakon corpses near Rogash's Manor, you conducted some investigations. Rogash had been absorbing draakons' orbs to enhance his own strength. After defeating Rogash, the guardian's group returned to base. However, they couldn't shake the uneasy feeling that was left following the destruction of the core in Exodor.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3" huntingZoneId="2000" prevId="1" villagerId="50000">
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">Thank you for coming.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I noticed something interesting while observing the draakons in Exodor.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"What is it?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Hasmina will tell you more.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4" huntingZoneId="2000" prevId="3" villagerId="50100">
        <Page social="0">Nice to see you again, &lt;PCNAME&gt;.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;A large number of draakon corpses have been discovered near Rogash's Manor in Exodor.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Someone seems to be removing the draakons' orbs. We can't just ignore this.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Let's get to the bottom of this together."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Thank you. I knew I could count on you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Let's leave at once.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Let me know when you're ready so we can use the teleportal to his garden.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Got it."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5" huntingZoneId="2000" prevId="4" villagerId="50101">
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">A draakon corpse.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The orb has been removed, as suspected.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;There is no doubt that someone must have removed it.&lt;BR&gt;Rogash's Manor is supposed to be empty. Let's head inside.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6" huntingZoneId="2000" prevId="5" villagerId="50120">
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">It looks like a journal kept by Rogash. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;400 days have passed since my arrival in Exodor.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I cannot stand another day in this dump filled with inferior peoples. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The only ray of light here is the beautiful Lumikan.&lt;BR&gt;I am prepared to do anything to help her realize her dream here. &lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Read the next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">It looks like a journey kept by Rogash.&lt;BR&gt;Lumikan asked me whether I would be able to absorb the orbs of draakons.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;She wondered if it wouldn't be difficult for a genius like myself. My only thought was to comply with her wish.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;It may be a crime to remove the orbs and commit genocide, but I will stop at nothing for her.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Turn several pages.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">It looks like a journal kept by Rogash.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Lumikan! Lumikan!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;She has been mutilated by a lowly people!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;They will feel my merciless vengeance, and they will be on their knees begging for death. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Read the next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">It looks like a journey kept by Rogash.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Orbs... I should develop a technique to remove the orbs for Lumikan.&lt;BR&gt;I have no choice but to learn new skills.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7" huntingZoneId="2000" prevId="6" villagerId="50102">
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">Orb absorption? New skills? What does this mean?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;According to this entry, Rogash has departed for Verrak Fortress. We should pursue him.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="8" huntingZoneId="2003" prevId="7" villagerId="80001">
        <Page social="0">The Fusion Laboratory is on the top floor of the Engine Room.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You can use this teleportal to reach it. Hurry.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="9" huntingZoneId="2003" prevId="8" villagerId="80002">
        <Page social="0">It was tough, but fortunately everything went well.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Don't forget Rogash's last words."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Rogash's words are indeed important.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;He spoke of a huge catastrophe that will befall us all...&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Oh! Shouldn't you report on the mission? &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We should hurry again.&lt;BR&gt;Ready?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="10" huntingZoneId="2000" prevId="9" villagerId="50000">
        <Page social="0">Rogash was trying to remove the orbs from his own kind in order to grow stronger...&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;A fitting end for the mad scientist.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
