<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
             xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd"
             id="5"
             huntingZoneId="25"
             voiceTypeId="0"
             xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">Mission Orders&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;PCNAME&gt;! Good news. Once you have completed your current mission, come find me in Tulufan. I have some good news from Velika for you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;-Baruch</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">Having annihilated the Lok believers, you returned to Velika.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Commander Seir organized a ceremony to celebrate your achievements, and Elleon complimented you for playing a pivotal role in bringing down the Scions of Lok.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3"
          huntingZoneId="66"
          prevId="1"
          villagerId="1001">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">There you are! Glad to see you made it back.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Velika's planned an event to celebrate the defeat of the Scions of Lok! They want you there right away. Troius will be waiting for you at the pegasus platform.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4"
          huntingZoneId="63"
          prevId="3"
          villagerId="1107">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">&lt;PCNAME&gt;, I heard about how you helped Elleon. Tremendous job! You have to tell Uriela you're here. She wanted to talk to you.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5"
          huntingZoneId="63"
          prevId="4"
          villagerId="1101">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">&lt;PCNAME&gt;! Everyone's talking about your gallantry and heroism today!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Commander Seir is waiting for you inside.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6"
          huntingZoneId="63"
          prevId="5"
          villagerId="1102">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">You've done great work, &lt;PCNAME&gt;! Your toppling the Scions of Lok—again—is no mean feat.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We are proud to have you in our ranks. You're a credit to the service and the entire federation! Elleon is looking for you as well. Don't keep him waiting.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7"
          huntingZoneId="63"
          prevId="6"
          villagerId="1169">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">It's hard to chastise a hero for being late to their own celebration, though we were thinking of ways to try!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Come! Let's not keep Seir waiting any longer. He so adores this sort of thing.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="8"
          huntingZoneId="63"
          prevId="7"
          villagerId="1169">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">Your courage helped uncover the traitorous Samael, the insidious Scions of Lok, and not one, but two threats to kill Velik.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The Valkyon Federation is still in danger—our work is never done, but with allies like you, we can dream of a brighter future. It's been a tremendous honor to work with you, &lt;PCNAME&gt;. We shall, as always, remember.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
