<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" id="1" huntingZoneId="20" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0" />
    <Text id="100" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">Goddess Velik, the guardian deity of Velika, wished to see you. You answered Priestess Ciebel's short questions, then were granted an audience with Velik. She warned you of a hidden threat to Velika and asked for your aid.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">Mission Orders&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Return to Velika at once and report to General Samael. All other orders are rescinded.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3" huntingZoneId="63" prevId="2" villagerId="1137">
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">Ah, &lt;PCNAME&gt;. It seems that Velik herself would like to reward you for the work you've done here. Velik's high priestess, {@linkcreature:63#1167#Ciebel}, is waiting for you near the idol of the goddess. I suggest you not keep her waiting.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4" huntingZoneId="63" prevId="3" villagerId="1167">
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">&lt;PCNAME&gt;, at last. Velik is seeking soldiers who are capable of more than simple obedience to orders. The Valkyon Federation needs champions—more than it might realize. What sort of soldier are you? &lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"What do you mean?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">Are you a dutiful follower or an independent thinker?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"..."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">We understand this may be confusing, from your perspective. But the gods live and work on different timelines than mortals.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You do not have to give an answer today.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;There are many steps ahead on the path to your destiny. Your answer will come to you in the fullness of time. Or not.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"What? I..."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">When the time comes, make a decision that you will not regret.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Now, are you ready to see the goddess in her sanctuary?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5" huntingZoneId="409" prevId="4" villagerId="1001">
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">&lt;PCNAME&gt;. I've watched your brief, but illustrious, career with interest. You've served with courage, honor, and, most importantly, compassion.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We have need of soldiers like you.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6" huntingZoneId="63" prevId="5" villagerId="1167">
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">You've returned. Remember what the goddess said to you. You must defend the city—and the Dream itself.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Return now to Samael. Farewell.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7" huntingZoneId="63" prevId="6" villagerId="1137">
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">Have you met the goddess?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"I have."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">You should be humbled. She doesn't meet with just anyone, you know. She must see something special in you. I wonder what. Hah!</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
