<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" id="51" huntingZoneId="30" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0" />
    <Text id="100" huntingZoneId="230" prevId="0" villagerId="1047">
        <Page social="0" />
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" huntingZoneId="230" prevId="0" villagerId="1047">
        <Page social="1">The repositories of wisdom record what has gone before. I suspect your friend in the Bastion, {@LinkCreature:71#1101$$Alais}, would rather know what is to come.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;As a way of thanking him for sending you to me, I will reveal where my clan has placed {@LinkCreature:230#1095#repositories of vision} across Balder's Refuge.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Learn the prophetic guidance those repositories possess, then tell Alais what you've learned.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I don't need to be a prophet to foresee him fainting on the spot.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3" huntingZoneId="230" prevId="2" villagerId="1095">
        <Page social="1">(This repository reads: Mystel, goddess of fate, warned the god Balder that great forces would soon destroy the heavenly realm and greatly diminish the surviving gods. Balder worried that the sun itself would not survive the coming destruction, so he summoned wise baraka, led by High Elder Vernicus and his child, Nandu.)&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;(The rest is written in a language you can't read.)</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4" huntingZoneId="230" prevId="2" villagerId="1096">
        <Page social="1">(This repository reads: The wise baraka built the temple to hold a gift from Balder, the Mirror of the Sun.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Should the world grow dark or enemies threaten it, a true hero will enter the temple and wield the mirror with righteousness.)&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;(The rest is written in a language you can't read.)</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5" huntingZoneId="230" prevId="2" villagerId="1097">
        <Page social="1">(This repository reads: The baraka grew worried, for despite their wisdom how could they know the identity of the true hero? The Goddess of Fate, Mystel, eased their fears, saying that the true hero's name would be inscribed upon the {@LinkCreature:226#1102$$cenotaph}, and the hero would bear a key.)&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;(The rest is written in a language you can't read.)</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6" huntingZoneId="230" prevId="2" villagerId="1098">
        <Page social="1">(This repository reads: The goddess Mystel further said, "I shall grant your clan longevity, so you may witness this day firsthand. As long as Balder's Pattern flows in the sky and the Lighthouse of the Sun shines, you shall be protected. Not until the temple opens will you age even an instant.")&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;(The rest is written in a language you can't read.)</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7" huntingZoneId="71" prevId="3" villagerId="1101">
        <Page social="1">{@LinkCreature:230#1047$$Nandu} showed you what?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;So Balder told the baraka to build a temple? We'd heard similar prophecies before.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Also, the part about Balder's Pattern—those glyphs and lines up in the sky. The Lighthouse of the Sun is new, though. Such power...so ancient, so immense. The rest of the Mysterium should hear about this right away.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="8" huntingZoneId="71" villagerId="1101">
        <Page social="0">You're looking for something. I can tell.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
