<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" id="12" huntingZoneId="213" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0" />
    <Text id="100" huntingZoneId="13" prevId="0" villagerId="8030">
        <Page social="0">After receiving Adria’s message, &lt;PCNAME&gt; visited the Island of Dawn.&lt;BR&gt;The island was beginning to show signs of recovery. The remaining divine essence had spread, and started to form small crystals across the island. Adria was thrilled by this progress, yet she had another concern. Thieves were after those crystals, so Adria asked &lt;PCNAME&gt; to hunt them down.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" huntingZoneId="13" prevId="0" villagerId="8030">
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">&lt;PCNAME&gt;, thanks to your efforts, the situation on the Island of Dawn is going well. The island is beginning to recover!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;It may be hard to believe after all those catastrophes, but it is true.&lt;BR&gt;Please stop by the Ruined Temple.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3" huntingZoneId="13" prevId="2" villagerId="8030">
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">&lt;PCNAME&gt;, you're here!&lt;BR&gt;I’m glad you came. I wanted to show you how the Island of Dawn is recovering, thanks to you.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Is everything going smoothly, then?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">It turned out, the divine essence of life wasn’t completely gone after all! Apparently, it was scattered across the island, and started to spring up again, in a solidified form. We’ve received a number of reports about crystallized essences all over the island.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;This is amazing progress.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"I'm glad to hear it."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">It's excellent news!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The divine essence is steadily returning. The crystals are still unstable and fragile, but they're reforming quickly. It truly is a sign that the island might regain its natural beauty again.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I could not ask for more.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"I'm looking forward to seeing it."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">You can see it right now!&lt;BR&gt;There's a field of crystals down the stairs behind me.&lt;BR&gt;I wanted to share this joyful news, especially with you. It wouldn't have been possible without you. And who knows? The goddess herself might return to us just to show you her gratitude. Silly thought...right? &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Anyway. I also have business. We have reports that there are thieves are after these crystals.&lt;BR&gt;They will not lay their hands on these crystals while I'm in charge! &lt;PCNAME&gt;, please, if you can, take care of them before they ruin everything.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"You can count on me."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4" huntingZoneId="13" prevId="3" villagerId="8030">
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">Back already? That's good news...right?&lt;BR&gt;Our research suggests that the crystals grant divine power to anyone who touches them. All our test volunteers said they will never forget the experience.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Our intelligence confirmed that caimans were after those crystals.&lt;BR&gt;My patrols caught them red-handed, but the caimans fled with incredible speed. &lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"I found them. They should trouble you no longer."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">By Velik!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You never cease to surprise us, you know that? This is embarrassing. We should put more cardio in the training menu.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;If you don’t mind, can you maybe just exterminate them on sight?&lt;BR&gt;The Island of Dawn is recovering at a good pace.&lt;BR&gt;I'd hate for a bunch of caiman thieves to bring the island's recovery to a grinding halt, just for the sake of a little divine essence.&lt;BR&gt;We need you to prevent this from happening.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"I'll do it."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
