<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
             xsi:schemaLocation="https://tera-arise.io/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd"
             id="1"
             huntingZoneId="2000"
             voiceTypeId="0"
             xmlns="https://tera-arise.io/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">&lt;PCNAME&gt;, although we failed to blast Exodor, we're still trying to find a way to stop it.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We have a new discovery about Exodor. Please come to me as soon as you see this order.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;— Ryshan</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">When explosives weren't the answer, the federation searched for a different solution to stop Exodor.&lt;BR&gt;With the help of the ecologist Amarre, the federation discovered a way to get inside Exodor. You went with Amarre and Titus to Exodor.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3"
          huntingZoneId="182"
          prevId="1"
          villagerId="6016">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">I've been expecting you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Although the Mysterium has thrown every resource it's got at investigating Exodor, we're still a long way off finding a way to stop Exodor from the outside.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;On top of that, Exodor seems to be making its way towards Velika.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;If that happens, the Valkyon Federation and all of Arborea will be in danger.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;But it's too early give up just yet. If it can't be destroyed from outside then there's got to be another way, right?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Is there another way?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">You'll never guess who's found a weak spot in the impenetrable fortress known as Exodor.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Amarre!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;According to her report, the Murderwings and Mournwings have a homing instinct.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Here, read it for yourself. &lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"What should I to do?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">There are some captured butterflies in this box. &lt;BR&gt;If you release them, you can fly to Exodor on them.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4"
          huntingZoneId="182"
          prevId="3"
          villagerId="6074">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">I never thought I'd see a Murderwing so closely. Thank you - both you and Amarre.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;It's a relief to have a way inside Exodor. You should be able to stop Exodor from the inside.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Titus and Amarre should be useful. Please take them with you and find a way to stop Exodor.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5"
          huntingZoneId="182"
          prevId="4"
          villagerId="6071">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">I guess I'm also suddenly joining this special unit... as the leader. Hehe.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I'm actually pleased and a little excited to be going to Exodor like this.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"It'll be dangerous."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">I know that. But the people have suffered enough from the effects of the crystals and these butterflies.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We must investigate Exodor and find a clue to end all this.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"I hope we do."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">Was someone else coming? Someone called Titus. We met each other just a while ago. He looks very confident about this.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6"
          huntingZoneId="182"
          prevId="5"
          villagerId="6072">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">What? Amarre? That ecologist is coming with us? On such a dangerous mission? This is no job for a scholar, if you ask me.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I won't stop her from coming, but I hope she doesn't get in our way.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7"
          huntingZoneId="2000"
          prevId="6"
          villagerId="20400">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">So this is Exodor...&lt;BR&gt;Fascinating!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We should take a look around.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
