<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
             xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd"
             id="1"
             huntingZoneId="27"
             voiceTypeId="0"
             xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="5"
              voiceTypeId="0">Mission Orders&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;A new request has arrived from Velika Headquarters. Please return to Velik immediately. A new mission awaits you at the Velika Headquarters.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;-Seir, Federation High Commander</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">Before leaving the Vanguard Initiative for Allemantheia, you visit Priestess Ciebel to learn the prophecy of your destiny and receive the blessing of the Goddess Velik from her. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Elleon advised you to seek out Fraya, commander of the high elf city of Allemantheia. Fraya welcomed you. She told you about the Federation and the high elf council of elders, and asked you to fight against anyone who opposed this alliance.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3"
          huntingZoneId="63"
          prevId="1"
          villagerId="1102">
        <Page social="5"
              voiceTypeId="0">Welcome back, &lt;PCNAME&gt;. It's been too long. Reports speak well of you, as I would expect.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;A request for assistance has come to us from Allemantheia, from a person no less notable than Fraya.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Who's Fraya?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="5"
              voiceTypeId="0">One of their most distinguished commanders.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I can offer no details, but be delicate and be wary.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"I will."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="5"
              voiceTypeId="0">Also, Ciebel has asked to speak with you before you leave.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4"
          huntingZoneId="63"
          prevId="3"
          villagerId="1167">
        <Page social="5"
              voiceTypeId="0">You have done well thus far, &lt;PCNAME&gt;. Velik wishes you to know that the shadow that threatened Velika now looms over the desert, and is darker than before.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Thank you for the warning."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="5"
              voiceTypeId="0">Be cautious in Allemantheia—be ever watchful for the danger that lurks in the shadows.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5"
          huntingZoneId="72"
          prevId="4"
          villagerId="1132">
        <Page social="5"
              voiceTypeId="0">Welcome to Allemantheia, &lt;PCNAME&gt;. Your flight went well?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The Desert Jewel is grateful for your assistance, as am I.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You must be wondering why you were summoned.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Very much."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="5"
              voiceTypeId="0">Power in Allemantheia is shared between the federation, the elders, and the Mysterium. It's a delicate balance. We need an outsider for some very specialized tasks, and your name was agreed upon by all three groups.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The Mysterium is pleased with you after your work in the Celestial Hills, and your own commanders exult over your cunning and courage.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"And the elders?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="5"
              voiceTypeId="0">More acquiescent than exultant. Still, that is a great victory. I don't want to give you the wrong impressions or mislead you.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Don't mind it."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="5"
              voiceTypeId="0">Fraya wants to speak with you directly before we begin. She's not only our greatest soldier, but a true inspiration. Speak to {@linkcreature:72#1103#Arshadh} first.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6"
          huntingZoneId="72"
          prevId="5"
          villagerId="1103">
        <Page social="5"
              voiceTypeId="0">Greetings, &lt;PCNAME&gt;. Fraya is waiting for you inside.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7"
          huntingZoneId="518"
          prevId="6"
          villagerId="1001">
        <Page social="5"
              voiceTypeId="0">Elleon's new friend arrives at last! Welcome to Allemantheia! Thank you for making the journey.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;There are a number of issues facing this city. Some require a deft touch—an outsider's touch. Sharing power in this city is something of a dance. It's intricate, it requires exquisite timing, and if one missteps, it hurts for a long time.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="8"
          huntingZoneId="518"
          prevId="7"
          villagerId="1001">
        <Page social="5"
              voiceTypeId="0">As an outsider, you have certain latitude in how you conduct business. Still, there are skeptics. Your work will reflect upon us all.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Not that there's any pressure.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
