<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" id="5" huntingZoneId="2003" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0" voiceTypeId="0">[Special Orders]&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;After you left Exodor, the Valkyon Federation established a base in Exodor to explore the area and keep an eye on Azart movements in the vicinity.&lt;BR&gt;We need to send supplies to this base, so come see me as soon as you get this.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">You met the Loadmaster to get supplies for Exodor, and returned to Exodor using the Door of Dimension.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3" huntingZoneId="63" prevId="1" villagerId="20006">
        <Page social="4">According to Dougal's message, an unstable teleportal appeared after the Black Core was destroyed.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We don't know what could come out from that teleportal... We must organize our defense.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Go to the Loadmasters and ask for support.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4" huntingZoneId="63" prevId="3" villagerId="1108">
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">That's the exact kind of job we're looking for. Leave it to me.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I'll ask the other Loadmasters for help.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5" huntingZoneId="63" prevId="4" villagerId="1567">
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">You've been to Exodor? That's quite surprising. A Door of Dimension to Exodor has opened. You should hear the details from Varlon.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I'll send you to Highwatch.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Say hi to Valron for me.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6" huntingZoneId="183" prevId="5" villagerId="4999">
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">I'm glad you came. One of our brothers went to Exodor after receiving a message from Dougal.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You can now travel to Exodor using our teleportal. Use the teleportal to go to Exodor and meet Dougal.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7" huntingZoneId="2000" prevId="6" villagerId="50000">
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">&lt;PCNAME&gt;Welcome!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I believe you already heard that a teleportal appeared after the Black Core was destroyed.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;There're also Azart remnants nearby. I want you to stop them.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
