<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" id="53" huntingZoneId="183" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">Find the {@linkcreature:183#2200#Dusty Tome} in Hall of Knowledge at Highwatch.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">&lt;PCNAME&gt; visits the Hall of Knowledge in Highwatch and reads about the history of the valkyries.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3" huntingZoneId="183" prevId="1" villagerId="2200">
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">&lt;BR&gt;Cold silence fills the air,&lt;BR&gt;nothing speaks but the rushing wind.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Glaive held tight,&lt;BR&gt;the last guardian reflects on her journey.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Unearned scars burn on her skin,&lt;BR&gt;a legacy of betrayal and lies.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The devas have fled north,&lt;BR&gt;and Clan Castanic searches for a new home.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Read the next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">&lt;BR&gt;Duty. Honor. Loyalty.&lt;BR&gt;Words, nothing more.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Our god is reviled, and our people ashamed.&lt;BR&gt;We must hide ourselves among our faithful.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Pass our stories down,&lt;BR&gt;mother to daughter, daughter to none.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Our pain will keep us together,&lt;BR&gt;wherever our people roam.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Read the next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">&lt;BR&gt;Daughter of Zuras, Child of Lok.&lt;BR&gt;My legacy is freedom, but always at a cost.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Carve the runes deep, sisters.&lt;BR&gt;One for each betrayal.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Choose your successor,&lt;BR&gt;train her well.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Take new names, take new lives.&lt;BR&gt;But never, ever, forget.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Read the next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">&lt;BR&gt;The day will come when the devas rise, and dark gods will live again.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;When our service is all but forgotten.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;On that day, take up your weapons, and fight!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Remember our Mother's words. Gentle, but firm.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;"Never conceal, and never reveal."&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;(The rest of the page is torn.)&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Read the next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0" />
    </Text>
    <Text id="4" huntingZoneId="183" prevId="3" villagerId="2201">
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">(The first and last sections of this book have been cut out, but a few of the remaining pages are still legible.)&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;...and our time in Deva Victrix is surely at an end.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Refugees from Kaiator have similar scars, and the priests all say the same thing.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Balder is dead.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;And we are to blame.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The crown was meant to honor him, but somehow...&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;There is nowhere we can go to escape our shame, and the guardians have abandoned us. Their glaives are gone, their houses empty, and we are left alone.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Read the next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">&lt;BR&gt;Lok, why have you abandoned us? Surely you were betrayed as well.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;And the guardians, your most strident defenders, have left us without protection.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;After so many years, are we to be wanderers again, like the humans?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The Matriarch is dead, and no-one will step forward to take her place.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;And the firstborn have taken their glaives away...&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Read the next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">&lt;BR&gt;Secondborn sons are trying to upstage our councils. Have they no shame? Our people need stability and wisdom if we are to survive these times.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Without a Matriarch everyone can trust, the only thing anyone can agree on is that we can no longer trust the gods, or those who follow them.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Kaia herself has offered us a place in her city, but even among the amani we will never be safe.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Wherever we go, one thing is clear.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Our new home must be a fortress, and we will never leave it again.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Read the next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">&lt;BR&gt;The new Matriarch is younger than all three of my daughters, and her hands are suspiciously calloused.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;No-one wants to ask her, but she moves too confidently to be just "a simple runecarver."&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;She brings with her stories of a new home, and our people are desperate enough to follow her there.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;If she is what I think she is, perhaps we have not been abandoned after all.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;When we arrive, when we are settled, perhaps Clan Castanic can find a way to forgive ourselves for our own cleverness. Or perhaps...&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;(The rest of the pages are missing.)&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close tome.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0" />
    </Text>
    <Text id="5" huntingZoneId="183" prevId="4" villagerId="2202">
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">&lt;BR&gt;I hummed the songs my mother's mother taught me under my breath as I wiped my runeglaive clean, but the enemy could no longer hear them.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I remember asking her once how many cultists I'd have to kill to free ourselves of Lok's legacy, but instead of a reply, she gave me a sad smile.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Because even as a child, I already knew the answer.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;All of them.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Read the next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">&lt;BR&gt;Up the hill from my midnight battle was a city of stones and bridges, and yet another community I'd been tasked to protect from the shadows.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I cut and carved my way across the world to get there, a place where my face and horns marked me as the enemy. East to west, south to north and back again, always hidden away from Balder's seeking eyes.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Inside its walled libraries, I learned of our lost kinsmen's descent into madness behind a wall of storms, and wept for generations of devas who died to preserve a fiction Clan Castanic discarded long ago.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The gods love no-one, even themselves.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Read the next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">&lt;BR&gt;I should have returned to Castanica months ago to make my report. But how could I turn my back on these people?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;They lived under the thumbs of monsters, yet still held their heads high.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;They sing songs of giants, and a world that never was.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;They bury the bodies I leave behind, and suffer in silence when my crimes are discovered.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I could not leave them, but neither could I stay.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Read the next page.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">&lt;BR&gt;In the end, as always, my runeglaive has made my decision for me.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Since coming here I've fought one too many enemies with acid in their veins.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;And as a member of a secret order long thought dead, I can't exactly stroll through town to get a replacement weapon.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Hopefully it will last long enough for me to return home, with a few of the records I've found here.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I've removed the more dangerous ones, and offer my own story in exchange for those who will come after me. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;After all, Never conceal, never reveal.</Page>
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0">&lt;BR&gt;So I leave you with this, my sister of the storm. The sour smell of blood stays with you, no matter how many times you wash.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The memories of dead, black eyes, of twisted bodies with the faces of friends, will never leave you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;My grandmother was wrong, and most likely yours as well. Patience, tolerance, acceptance...these are not our ways.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We are no longer the guardians of history. We are vengeance, the choosers of the slain.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We are valkyries, and as foretold in prophecy, thrice carved in stone, our time will come again.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Close tome.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4" voiceTypeId="0" />
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
