<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" id="32" huntingZoneId="21" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0" />
    <Text id="100" huntingZoneId="221" prevId="0" villagerId="1021">
        <Page social="0" />
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" huntingZoneId="221" prevId="0" villagerId="1021">
        <Page social="4">After careful study, these fragments indicate an intense love of the gods. So much so that it eventually turned to bitterness, then rebelliousness.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;When love turns to hate, the consequences can be devastating. Do you know of what I speak?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"The giants?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="4">Impressive, and quite correct. The giants built a powerful civilization and went to war against the very gods they formerly loved.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I saw some remains in the ruins. Artifacts and bones usually go together in my experience, so why don't you run in and see if you can recover them. Perhaps we'll shed some more light on this mystery!</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3" huntingZoneId="221" prevId="2" villagerId="1021">
        <Page social="4">Let's see what you brought back!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Fascinating. These are giant bones, but there's some strange aura of magic about them. Let me try a small bit of magic...&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Divine magic. STRONG divine magic. These bones are from the Day of Fire, the day the gods united and smote the entire giant empire! This is quite a find! Thank you, &lt;PCNAME&gt;!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I promise to give you credit in my paper!</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4" huntingZoneId="221" villagerId="1021">
        <Page social="0">I feel certain the key to this mystery lies with those bones I saw. Bring them back to me and I'll examine them more closely!</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
