<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
             xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd"
             id="2"
             huntingZoneId="3107"
             voiceTypeId="0"
             xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">Where has Dakuryon gone with the Argon Priest?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">You set off for the Desolarus Testing Grounds to find Dakuryon.&lt;BR&gt;Upon arrival, you discovered that Desolarus had been argonized by Dakuryon and Armen. You defeated the argonized Desolarus.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3"
          huntingZoneId="1"
          prevId="1"
          villagerId="30003">
        <Page social="0">This is allow us to teleport to Dakuryon's hideout.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4"
          huntingZoneId="3107"
          prevId="3"
          villagerId="30000">
        <Page social="0">Dakuryon carried out an experiment and transformed Desolarus into an argon.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I will catch that sick Durion and make him pay for that.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;He might have gotten away from me again this time, but I won't make any mistakes next time.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;But first we have to take care of Desolarus.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Are you ready?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5"
          huntingZoneId="1"
          prevId="4"
          villagerId="10012">
        <Page social="0">The invasion of the argons has started again.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Do you know what their target is?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Possibly the Spring of Arun?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Yes, I suspect that too.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The Spring of Arun has divine power.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;With it, they could do whatever they wanted.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I hope my suspicion is wrong, but I fear that the argons want to use that power to bring Manahan to Arborea.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The Spring of Arun must be their next target. &lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Together we can prevent that."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Yes! If the Spring of Arun were controlled by the argons... I don't even want to think what would happen then.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Only with your help can we defeat them.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Come with us, &lt;PCNAME&gt;! "We can do it together for sure!"</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
