<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" id="4" huntingZoneId="1" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">&lt;PCNAME&gt;, an urgent matter requires my attention.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I've left something there.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I won't be gone long.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">While investigating the argons' activities in Baldera in the name of the goddess Kaia, you discovered that Shade was actually Dakuryon. &lt;BR&gt;Meanwhile, Dakuryon kidnapped Rhodos to perform experiments on him to strengthen his own body and to attempt to make contact with Manahan.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3" huntingZoneId="1" prevId="1" villagerId="10205">
        <Page social="0">*cough* &lt;PCNAME&gt;, an urgent matter requires my attention.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I've left something there.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I won't be gone long. &lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"What is it?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">I've forgotten my research materials. *cough* *cough*&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;It's all in my head, but still I shouldn't just leave it lying around. I'll be right back. You don't need to accompany me.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4" huntingZoneId="1" prevId="3" villagerId="10105">
        <Page social="0">Shade has been gone for a while now to get his materials.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;He didn't seem to be in the best of shape. Maybe something has happened?&lt;BR&gt;We should probably go look for him, but we have to set out for the Spring of Arun on Kaia's orders. This is a dilemma.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;What should we do?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5" huntingZoneId="1" prevId="4" villagerId="10005">
        <Page social="0">Shade said he'd be back soon, but he still hasn't returned. We can't wait any longer for him.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;When I think of the argons roaming around near the Spring of Arun, it only leads me to one conclusion: that they want to exploit the spring for their own purposes. We cannot sit by and leave the Spring of Arun to the argons. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;If we leave a note for Shade telling him where we're going, we can surely meet up with him later.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6" huntingZoneId="1" prevId="5" villagerId="11005">
        <Page social="0">You want to know where Shade went?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Haha. Well, I know how whether that rude guy's name is Shade, but a castanic man in a blue robe passed by here. He was complaining that my big body was getting in his way. He hurled that and other insults at me. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I never thought I would encounter someone so nasty here in Balderon, on my search for the true home of the Baraka.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7" huntingZoneId="1" prevId="6" villagerId="10403">
        <Page social="0">I am here at the shaman's behest.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I was told that you might be in trouble. That's why I came.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Your castanic friend hauled someone off to Ruinweald. He was young and tall, but he didn't appear to be conscious.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Perhaps they were on their way to the Spring of Arun?&lt;BR&gt;What are you going to do now? Do you want to set off for the spring to find your castanic friend?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I'll help you whatever you decide to do.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="8" huntingZoneId="3045" prevId="7" villagerId="2000">
        <Page social="0">What kind of place is this? I've never heard of a place before where argons and demokrons conduct experiments together. We should investigate this place. Please take them out.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="9" huntingZoneId="3045" prevId="8" villagerId="4000">
        <Page social="0">Rhodos isn't moving. You take Rhodos out of the test chamber.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="10" huntingZoneId="3045" prevId="9" villagerId="4001">
        <Page social="0">Rhodos's heart is no longer beating. We're too late to save Rhodos.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="11" huntingZoneId="3045" prevId="10" villagerId="3003">
        <Page social="0">Is Dakuryon not dead after all? I was foolish enough to lose a cherished friend because Shade had concealed his true identity.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;That voice... When I heard that voice, I couldn't move a muscle. That voice was not of this world. What was that? That's extremely disturbing. &lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Pull yourself together."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">You're right. We should return to Balderon first and analyze the situation.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Let's go.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="12" huntingZoneId="1" prevId="11" villagerId="10012">
        <Page social="0">It can be no coincidence that we discovered argons, Baldera, and then the Spring of Arun, can it?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;It is clear that it's him who spoke to us through Rhodos.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="13" huntingZoneId="1" prevId="12" villagerId="10600">
        <Page social="0">My sword.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;It is as you think. It is the god Manahan, who was banished by the gods of creation. Since his prison was becoming weaker and weaker, he was able to show his face again in Arborea. However, he still cannot draw on his full strength. That's why he must have tasked Dakuryon with finding his son Armen Manaya.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;If Dakuryon and Armen join forces, they will gather the argons here to resurrect Manahan. &lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"You know that Dakuryon is alive?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Yes.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Have you seen Dakuryon's depot, full of his clones? I learned that Dakuryon is storing his memories and implanting them in clones. This way, he can be resurrected as many times as he likes.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;A repository full of clones has already been destroyed elsewhere. Judging from the large number of clones, it seems like he has to change bodies frequently. He surely must be nervous.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;My sword, what are your thoughts about fate? &lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Have the gods of creation already decided my fate?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">It may be that our fates are already laid out. But it may also be that it makes us stronger.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;But none of this matters as I firmly believe that you will overcome any challenge. My sword, I must return to my station.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
