<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
             xsi:schemaLocation="https://tera-arise.io/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd"
             id="2"
             huntingZoneId="84"
             voiceTypeId="0"
             xmlns="https://tera-arise.io/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">Report what is happening in Granarkus to Seir so that the Federation can act accordingly. Let's go to Velika and find Commander Seir.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">After reporting to Commander Seir about the situation in Granarkus, he says that Manahan seems to be pulling the strings behind the scenes, just as the goddess Velik had suspected.&lt;BR&gt;You go and report to the goddess Velik. She is sure that Manahan is responsible for these events and decides to take a look at his memories.&lt;BR&gt;You go to the Dakuryon Depot to find the totem containing Manahan's power and the mysterious crystal, and bring them to the goddess Velik.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3"
          huntingZoneId="63"
          prevId="1"
          villagerId="1102">
        <Page social="0">&lt;PCNAME&gt;! I'm glad you're here. I was about to call you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;By the look on your face, this is something serious. What has happened?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;You report on the situation in Granarkus.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Hmm, a phenomenon like this occurred in Granarkus... It seems to have something to do with what the goddess Velik was talking about.&lt;BR&gt;If you ask me, Manahan is responsible for the goings-on in Granarkus. Regardless, the goddess Velik has been waiting for you regarding Manahan.&lt;BR&gt;Go see the goddess Velik quickly.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4"
          huntingZoneId="63"
          prevId="3"
          villagerId="1265">
        <Page social="0">Ah, &lt;PCNAME&gt;!&lt;BR&gt;The goddess Velik is waiting for you.&lt;BR&gt;Go to Velik's Sanctuary and meet the goddess.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5"
          huntingZoneId="3049"
          prevId="4"
          villagerId="1001">
        <Page social="0">I've been expecting you.&lt;BR&gt;Manahan's once weak energy is growing stronger by the day.&lt;BR&gt;If it carries on like this, Arborea will be in big danger.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;You report what has happened in Granarkus to the goddess.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Manahan will have something to do with that too.&lt;BR&gt;We need to look at Manahan's memories to find out what he is up to. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I will dispatch you to the Dakuryon Depot to find an object there that contains his power.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Let me know when you're ready.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6"
          huntingZoneId="3052"
          prevId="5"
          villagerId="1101">
        <Page social="0">&lt;PCNAME&gt;! I received Commander Seir's message and waited here for you.&lt;BR&gt;We need to find an object here that contains Manahan's power, is that right?&lt;BR&gt;Manahan's eyes have already turned up here, so we're bound to find an object with his power too.&lt;BR&gt;Let's go in.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7"
          huntingZoneId="3052"
          prevId="6"
          villagerId="1102">
        <Page social="0">If you are after the forbidden power, stop! &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Manahan was cursed by the ancient gods. His power is not desirable. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;If you are the guardian of Arborea, you must be vigilant.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Monitor Manahan and his new power carefully.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="8"
          huntingZoneId="3052"
          prevId="7"
          villagerId="1104">
        <Page social="0">I'm glad you found the object... but what kind of crystal is that?&lt;BR&gt;The shield seems to have been there to prevent Manahan's power from falling into the wrong hands.&lt;BR&gt;I don't think Dakuryon is responsible for this. But who is then?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"It would be better to ask the goddess Velik."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">We must bring Manahan's Totem to the goddess Velik as quickly as possible.&lt;BR&gt;I will send you directly to Velik's Sanctuary.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Let me know when you're ready.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="9"
          huntingZoneId="3049"
          prevId="8"
          villagerId="1001">
        <Page social="0">I've been waiting for you.&lt;BR&gt;I can sense Manahan's energy in this object.&lt;BR&gt;We can use it to see his memories and uncover what he is plotting.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
