<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
             xsi:schemaLocation="https://tera-arise.io/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd"
             id="2"
             huntingZoneId="1"
             voiceTypeId="0"
             xmlns="https://tera-arise.io/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">The barrier that was blocking access to Baldera has disappeared.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Go to Baldera.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">You found the Spring of Arun, which was previously thought to be a legend from the Ruinweald. The creatures near the Spring of Arun have been poisoned as it is contaminated. You destroyed Akasha's Machine, the cause of the pollution, and went to Balderon.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3"
          huntingZoneId="1"
          prevId="1"
          villagerId="10200">
        <Page social="0">For this place to have remained hidden by the barrier...!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;It has preserved ancient Arborea, just as it was long before our time.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Amazing! &lt;PCNAME&gt;, I would like to ask a favor of you. Help me study this area. I'll take care of the plants, and you deal with the unicorns and ghilliedhus.&lt;BR&gt;I need a few samples of each.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4"
          huntingZoneId="1"
          prevId="3"
          villagerId="10201">
        <Page social="0">Excellent!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Can I see the samples you brought me? Hmm... I see... *cough*&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The same constituents as we know from creatures in the Ruinweald. Maybe that's why the unicorns and the ghilliedhus have become aggressive.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Why are the same constituents found in both creatures, despite the fact that they are completely unrelated?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5"
          huntingZoneId="1"
          prevId="3"
          villagerId="10201">
        <Page social="0">I need more samples. Please bring me some.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6"
          huntingZoneId="1"
          prevId="4"
          villagerId="10002">
        <Page social="0">Did we really find the Spring of Arun?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;According to legend, the water flowed from Arun's heart, leaving behind a spring. Every child in Arborea knows the tale.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;And this is that spring there in front of us? Don't you get the feeling that something isn't right with the spring? I don't sense the healing influence of the gods here nor from the spring.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7"
          huntingZoneId="1"
          prevId="6"
          villagerId="10300">
        <Page social="0">My horoscope predicted that I'd meet an important person standing by the water today. It is fate that we met.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Don't be afraid, &lt;PCRACE&gt;.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;As you can see, we pose no danger. Quite the opposite: we need your help.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"What can I do for you?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Let me explain from the beginning.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We Shurians used to be very powerful and possessed magic powers. Even the giants from the holy realm were afraid of us and gave up trying to conquer the northern regions. After the age of the giants, we helped Akasha take control of the Spring of Arun. That was the beginning of the end for us. Akasha constructed a machine with which we Shurians could use the power of the spring. In doing so, we were slowly but steadily poisoned by the spring.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;That machine and our greed cost us everything. And so our proud culture perished. The power of the spring makes everyone who uses it completely dependent. You lose your mind and forget about everything else.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Please help our tribe.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"How can I help you?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Akasha's Machine is located near the spring. Sabotage the machine. We are bound by an ancient pact, so there's nothing we can do ourselves.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;If you sabotage the machine, we'll help you get out of here.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="8"
          huntingZoneId="1"
          prevId="7"
          villagerId="10300">
        <Page social="0">You have my thanks. But even now the machine has been destroyed, it will take some time to clear the spring of the contamination. The machine may have been the cause of the contamination, but the self-healing of the spring is a very slow process.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Once the spring is completely pure again, we too will be able to return to our former glory.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We have one last request for you. This Tombstone Charm needs to be placed at the North Gate.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We fear that misfortune may befall our tribe, so we've crafted a charm.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="9"
          huntingZoneId="1"
          prevId="8"
          villagerId="10401">
        <Page social="0">You go ahead and I will follow you.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="10"
          huntingZoneId="1"
          prevId="8"
          villagerId="10500">
        <Page social="0">The barrier disappeared some time ago.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The area has been deserted for quite some time, which is why many people are coming now, hoping to find undiscovered riches. Head to Balderon. Balderon will soon be transformed into a thriving metropolis of Arborea. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Take this path and you will come across a large bridge. It'll take you to Balderon.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"What do you know about the argons?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">The argons appear near the ruins from time to time.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;They don't do anything to us, other than roam around and then disappear again.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="11"
          huntingZoneId="1"
          prevId="10"
          villagerId="10004">
        <Page social="0">We're in Balderon! I didn't know there was an ancient city here.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Hoakha and I will go look for Kaia and tell her about the Spring of Arun.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;PCNAME&gt;, please ask the villagers whether argons have been sighted in Baldera.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="12"
          huntingZoneId="1"
          prevId="11"
          villagerId="10204">
        <Page social="0">Fantastic!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Isn't it great that we found such a beautiful city?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"We should focus on Hasmina's mission."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">What? You can do that on your own later, can't you?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I want to explore this beautiful city a little more. We can meet up again later. Hmm... perhaps on the bridge over there.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
