<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
             xsi:schemaLocation="https://tera-arise.io/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd"
             id="1"
             huntingZoneId="618"
             voiceTypeId="0"
             xmlns="https://tera-arise.io/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">I've heard that the Argons are back in Exodor.&lt;PCNAME&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You'll have to get stronger if you're going to fight them.&lt;BR&gt;Come to the Blacksmith's Workshop.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Goddess Kaia.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">When the goddess Kaia learned of the situation in Exodor she was disturbed, sensing Balder's power in Azart's items and the Argons.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;She recognized that the source of this power was an artificial sun, and devised a way of extracting the power in order to make powerful weapons from it.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3"
          huntingZoneId="79"
          prevId="1"
          villagerId="1501">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">A teleportal leading to the Blacksmith's Workshop.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Make sure you're ready.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4"
          huntingZoneId="411"
          prevId="3"
          villagerId="7000">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">The Argons are back!&lt;BR&gt;Why didn't you tell me about this right away, &lt;PCNAME&gt;?!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I was convinced that we'd driven them out once and for all... and now they're turning Kelsaik into an Argon just to make our lives difficult! This is really infuriating!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;They're very strong, which is why I sent for you; I want to give you some powerful equipment.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"What kind of equipment?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">With Sikander's help, I've built a new anvil.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Any equipment made using this anvil is stronger than ordinary equipment.&lt;BR&gt;Aren't you curious how strong this new equipment is?&lt;BR&gt;Talk to Fovarth to find out more.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5"
          huntingZoneId="411"
          prevId="4"
          villagerId="5017">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">The anvil was forged in a flame ignited by Kaia's power!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Using this anvil, it's now possible to craft new equipment that has Kaia's power vested within it.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Check you've got the necessary materials to make the equipment.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
