<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
             xsi:schemaLocation="https://tera-arise.io/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd"
             id="21"
             huntingZoneId="1"
             voiceTypeId="0"
             xmlns="https://tera-arise.io/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">Hopefully Vella can regain her strength quickly.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">While you wait with Hasmina for Vella to regenerate and the teleportal to be repaired, you chat to Hasmina and get to know her better.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Hasmina opens up and tells you about her older twin sister Hellen.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3"
          huntingZoneId="72"
          prevId="1"
          villagerId="40200">
        <Page social="0">I hope it's not bad news for Vella, even though her body temperature was so low.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Let's take the destroyed teleportal to the Mysterium.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4"
          huntingZoneId="72"
          prevId="3"
          villagerId="1111">
        <Page social="0">Vella said you'd bring us the teleportal?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Hmm, it won't be easy to fully restore the teleportal, but I'll do my best. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Hang on a minute.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5"
          huntingZoneId="72"
          prevId="4"
          villagerId="40000">
        <Page social="0">Thank you for saving me.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I was dressed appropriately, but it was much colder in Frost Reach than I'd expected. A moment later and I'd have been done for.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Thank you.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"What happened?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">I'm guessing you know Dakuryon has several depots?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;After I received the Federation's order to find Dakuryon, I searched for one of his locked storehouses. While doing so, I heard that he wanted to establish a new base in Westonia.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I searched high and low in Frost Reach and came across a suspicious teleportal.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;When I touched it, the teleportal broke into pieces and I passed out from incredible pain.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Pain?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">At first I thought the energy of the destroyed magic stone had caused the pain. However, the sorcerer who treated me said he had found a glyph on my body.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The glyph is different from the ones Dakuryon uses to control the Demokrons.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;But no one knows this glyph yet, so we aren't sure who made it or what purpose it serves.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;What happened to the teleportal anyway?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"It's being repaired as we speak."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Okay.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Then we should wait until the teleportal has been fixed.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6"
          huntingZoneId="72"
          prevId="5"
          villagerId="1111">
        <Page social="0">The teleportal has been repaired but, oddly, it can't be activated.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The glyph on Vella's body appears to be the power that was keeping the teleportal active. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;If you decipher the glyph, we'll be able to find out the teleportal's destination.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;One person should return the teleportal to its original location, while the others wait until the glyph is deciphered.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7"
          huntingZoneId="72"
          prevId="6"
          villagerId="40301">
        <Page social="0">I will return the teleportal to Frost Reach.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Please wait here with Hasmina until you've found a way to activate the teleportal, then follow me.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="8"
          huntingZoneId="72"
          prevId="7"
          villagerId="40206">
        <Page social="0">It's bound to take longer to decipher the glyph than to repair the teleportal. Why don't you take a little break?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Fancy some fresh air?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="9"
          huntingZoneId="72"
          prevId="8"
          villagerId="40202">
        <Page social="0">The air is very pleasant today.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Allemantheia is always a wonderful sight.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Will you walk with me this way a little?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="10"
          huntingZoneId="72"
          prevId="9"
          villagerId="40100">
        <Page social="0">Hellen! Oh my goodness, Hellen?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I heard you died fighting the Argons, but I never believed it.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;There was no way an excellent sorcerer like you could meet her end in battle against Argons.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I knew you were still alive!&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Her name is Hasmina, not Hellen."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Hasmina?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I'm sorry. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;My apologies please.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You look so like Hellen. I got you mixed up.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="11"
          huntingZoneId="72"
          prevId="10"
          villagerId="40204">
        <Page social="0">Hellen is my older twin sister. She was an eminent sorcerer in Allemantheia.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;During the Argon War, she set out to research the Argons, but she disappeared without a trace. Later, a scrap of her clothing was found.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Sorcerers are able to sense the magic of other sorcerers, even if they are far away. But no one could sense her magic.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;So it was concluded that she had died in battle with the Argons.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I never thought I'd lose my parents, then my sister to the Argon.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Is everything alright?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">All these events took their toll on me.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Time has healed some wounds, but I still feel sad when I think of her.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;There's just so much here in Allemantheia that reminds me of her.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;There's a secret spot near the elevator up ahead where I used to hide when I wanted some time alone after an argument with my sister.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;You listen in silence.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Oh, I just thought of somewhere.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Will you go there with me?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="12"
          huntingZoneId="72"
          prevId="11"
          villagerId="40205">
        <Page social="0">It's the place my sister and I liked best.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The fountain alone is amazing, but the sound of trickling water always made me feel good.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;It was fun watching the people of Allemantheia come through the gate, too.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"You got on really well with your sister."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Yeah.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Hellen was the reason I came to Allemantheia and became a warrior.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The sorcerers in Allemantheia saw my sister's potential and urged her to come here, but she said she would only come if I came with her.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;She was the only thing I had left in this world... and now I'm all alone.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
