<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
             xsi:schemaLocation="https://tera-arise.io/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd"
             id="22"
             huntingZoneId="1"
             voiceTypeId="0"
             xmlns="https://tera-arise.io/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">Some time has passed.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">The teleportal has been repaired, and you have gone to the Ice Throne with your comrades.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Dakuryon has built a throne in his honor in an icy place where he keeps his experiment.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;He cruelly turned Hasmina's sister into a monster, which ultimately led to her death.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3"
          huntingZoneId="72"
          prevId="1"
          villagerId="40205">
        <Page social="0">Some time has passed.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The glyph should have been fully deciphered by now, right?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Let's head to the Mysterium.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Let's teleport there. Are you ready to go?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4"
          huntingZoneId="72"
          prevId="3"
          villagerId="1111">
        <Page social="0">The glyph has just been deciphered.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;A method was found to convert the glyph from Vella's body into a gemstone to activate the teleportal.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Activate the teleportal using the gemstone made from the deciphered glyph.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"How do I activate the teleportal?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Exposing the gemstone to extreme cold will connect the portal to the destination.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Hoakha has already left for Frost Reach to set up the teleportal. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Go and join him.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5"
          huntingZoneId="34"
          prevId="4"
          villagerId="40100">
        <Page social="0">So you've found a way to activate the teleportal.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The orb gives the teleportal its power.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6"
          huntingZoneId="3056"
          prevId="5"
          villagerId="40001">
        <Page social="0">You can feel the icy coldness of this place all over your body.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;It must be an extremely important secret for the gatekeeper himself to be present.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Let's take out the enemies and keep moving.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7"
          huntingZoneId="3056"
          prevId="6"
          villagerId="40002">
        <Page social="0">There seems to be some kind of special device.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You need to time it right so you can jump when the ice mine explodes and make it out of here.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="8"
          huntingZoneId="3056"
          prevId="7"
          villagerId="40105">
        <Page social="0">There are no words to express the grief we feel when a friend dies.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We must remember what the two sisters achieved.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Let us first return to Kaiator and report to Kaia.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="9"
          huntingZoneId="84"
          prevId="8"
          villagerId="40300">
        <Page social="0">You must notify Headquarters of Hasmina's death.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
