<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
             xsi:schemaLocation="https://tera-arise.io/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd"
             id="12"
             huntingZoneId="172"
             voiceTypeId="0"
             xmlns="https://tera-arise.io/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1"
          huntingZoneId="172"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="1301">
        <Page social="4">I followed your trail and that got me here safely. Judging by such a friendly reception, you must have accomplished quite a bit here already.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;There's a rumor going around the camp that some strange ruins have been spotted nearby. I'm sure the sky cruiser isn't far from here! &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We should take a short breather and then head for the sky cruiser.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">Rhodos reports to you on the Khirian situation in Northern Arun. You help Rhodos to convince the Parthians, but you fail. (There was no improvement in sight.)</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3"
          huntingZoneId="172"
          prevId="1"
          villagerId="1301">
        <Page social="4">Paesyn wants to talk to you if you have a moment.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4"
          huntingZoneId="172"
          prevId="3"
          villagerId="1100">
        <Page social="4">This is why I like you! You saved the day!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I've seen several pieces of Intrepid's wreckage. I'll check them over. Maybe impress Zolyn a bit. Get her to like me!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Since my poem didn't cheer her up, I drew a portrait of her. Could you deliver it? Please?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5"
          huntingZoneId="172"
          prevId="4"
          villagerId="1102">
        <Page social="4">I heard you saved Madat. Not bad. You're a fine soldier.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Paesyn drew this for you."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">I take it back.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Stop wasting my time with this nonsense. What is with that silly engineer? Doesn't he have work to do?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6"
          huntingZoneId="172"
          prevId="5"
          villagerId="1301">
        <Page social="4">Have you seen where Paesyn went by any chance?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"He's investigating the wreckage."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Well, we must press on.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7"
          huntingZoneId="172"
          prevId="6"
          villagerId="1206">
        <Page social="4">The way ahead will not be easy. You are new to Val Oriyn, so hear our grim tale.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="8"
          huntingZoneId="172"
          prevId="7"
          villagerId="1206">
        <Page social="4">We, the Khirians, resist the archdevas, but most of my kind are enslaved. We refer to them as the Parthia.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;They have a camp nearby, but I don't know if they'll let us pass without a fight.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"I'll talk to them."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">I hope diplomacy works for you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Look for Pariya. The Parthia respect her, but be careful.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;She's dangerous.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="9"
          huntingZoneId="172"
          prevId="8"
          villagerId="1015">
        <Page social="0">Hatishna? You believe such a popori tale?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;No one stands against Lord Dakuryon. You too shall kneel before him!</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="10"
          huntingZoneId="172"
          prevId="9"
          villagerId="1200">
        <Page social="4">Oh, &lt;PCNAME&gt;! You're here? Great!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Did Zolyn like the picture? I worked for days on it. What did she say?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"She didn't care for it."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">She probably doesn't appreciate my abstract realism. I studied art for two days in Velika, so I know all about it.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
