<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
             xsi:schemaLocation="https://tera-arise.io/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd"
             id="1"
             huntingZoneId="3206"
             voiceTypeId="0"
             xmlns="https://tera-arise.io/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">I'm sending you this message from Mount Tyrannas, which is as harsh and dismal as a Frost Dragon's breath.&lt;BR&gt;After the Exodor Core was destroyed, I thought the worst of it was behind us but strange things have been happening in Arborea lately.&lt;BR&gt;Evil that was believed to have been sealed off seems to be appearing once again. Please get to the bottom of these rumors.&lt;BR&gt;I'll wait for you in the Citadel of Torment.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Vella</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">The rift between the dimensions has grown unstable after the Exodor Core was destroyed.&lt;BR&gt;This crack is allowing ancient evils that had been sealed away to run amok once again. Please put a stop to them.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3"
          huntingZoneId="32"
          prevId="1"
          villagerId="9000">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">As it said in the message, ancient evil is running rampant here again.&lt;BR&gt;Thulsa is said to have created these monsters using necromancy in the Citadel of Torment.&lt;BR&gt;These creatures were supposed to have been dealt with or disappeared, but they've started appearing again.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"How could this happen?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">The Mysterium is working on the assumption that the destruction of the Exodor Core had a significant impact, enough to destabilize the rift between the dimensions.&lt;BR&gt;Gardan is madness incarnate.&lt;BR&gt;That such evil has reappeared can only be a bad omen.&lt;BR&gt;Please restore peace to Acarum.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4"
          huntingZoneId="233"
          prevId="3"
          villagerId="9001">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">This is the entrance to the Killing Grounds where Gardan is holed up.&lt;BR&gt;Garan, who takes particular delight in a good bloodbath, condemns innocent souls here.&lt;BR&gt;These poor souls are said to still roam this place.&lt;BR&gt;If you're ready to face Gardan, use this teleportal.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5"
          huntingZoneId="233"
          prevId="4"
          villagerId="9001">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">It truly is fantastic that you've defeated Gardan.&lt;BR&gt;We can all breathe easy again for now.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;However, we don't know what other consequences this unstable rift between the dimensions might bring.&lt;BR&gt;Arborea might be doomed to fall.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Not while I've got anything to do with it."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Hehe. That's true.&lt;BR&gt;We can rely on you.&lt;BR&gt;I really am grateful you're on our side.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
