<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
             xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd"
             id="4"
             huntingZoneId="181"
             voiceTypeId="0"
             xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1"
          huntingZoneId="183"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="2033">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">Hey, you! You were in the Vault of Oriyn!&lt;BR&gt;Can I ask a little favor of you if you're already heading to Havenstone?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Our job is to guard the Southern Gate and Havenstone, and to eliminate any invading demokron shock troopers. &lt;BR&gt;As I'm sure you know, we lost Verikam and Oriyn's Arcana at the same time. Since everyone is searching for Verikam and Oriyn's Arcana, forces are stretched thin.&lt;BR&gt;Currently, we're not in a position to face the demokron shock troopers. To ensure the safety of Highwatch, we've been ordered to hold the fort here.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We're not able to completely wipe out a single demokron shock trooper anyway. &lt;BR&gt;The problem is that the demokron shock troopers pose a danger to ordinary citizens.&lt;BR&gt;It has come to my ear that you are extremely competent. You wouldn't be able to deal with this threat, would you?&lt;BR&gt;If you were to eliminate a few demokrons on your way to the Qeldar Station, we'll gladly reward you. &lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Leave it to me."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">After the Vault of Oriyn incident, all the military forces of Highwatch gathered to find Verikam and protect the city. &lt;BR&gt;However, the demokron forces that invaded Havenstone were too powerful, so you rushed to the guards' aid.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3"
          huntingZoneId="181"
          prevId="1"
          villagerId="1031">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">Ah! Yes, you are &lt;PCNAME&gt;, the visitor from the south.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Thank you for helping us.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"I hope what I am doing is helping."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
