<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
             xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd"
             id="4"
             huntingZoneId="15"
             voiceTypeId="0"
             xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1"
          huntingZoneId="216"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="1028">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">It's time to enter the manor. We should split up. We'll go over the details in the cave. Got it?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Here's an Earth-shattering K Bomb in case of an emergency. Find the dementalith generator and destroy it. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Any problems, use the bomb. It's the last one though, so use it wisely. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;See the cave over there? Head inside. &lt;BR&gt;May the goddess watch over you.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">Jelena's plan got you into the manor. While Jelena cleared the way, you killed the vampir duke and duchess, found the device that produced the dementaliths-and blew it to bits.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;A Scion priestess, Akia, vowed revenge for your meddling. By the time you killed her pet arachnen, she'd escaped, but you forged a strong friendship with Jelena.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3"
          huntingZoneId="3002"
          prevId="1"
          villagerId="1001">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">Shhh! They're right up those stairs!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Can you feel that tingling? Right in the back of your neck? That must be magic from their device. Blast, it's strong! We must be quick.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Okay, are you ready?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4"
          huntingZoneId="3002"
          prevId="3"
          villagerId="1001">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">You'll be making a lot of noise, so I'll disable their alarms, and meet at the ladder to the ground floor.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;If anyone—or anything—gives you trouble, cut them down and let the Dream sort it out.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5"
          huntingZoneId="3002"
          prevId="4"
          villagerId="1005">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">You go crash {@linkcreature:3002#10#Duchess Tirania} and {@linkcreature:3002#13#Duke Volperon}'s little party.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I'll rig the temple door to open when they die. Then we can put an end to this mess.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6"
          huntingZoneId="3002"
          villagerId="22">
        <Page social="0">All right. It's time to take out that device. Hum a song or count as high as you can-anything to keep your mind focused. Just make sure you destroy the target!</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7"
          huntingZoneId="216"
          prevId="5"
          villagerId="1028">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">Is this the end of Sinestral Manor?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We got rid of the duke and duchess and destroyed the dementalith generator. All in a day's work, eh? Great job in there!</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
