<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
             xsi:schemaLocation="https://tera-arise.io/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd"
             id="3"
             huntingZoneId="84"
             voiceTypeId="0"
             xmlns="https://tera-arise.io/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">The goddess Velik wants to look at Manahan's memories using an object that contains his power. Look at the memories and thwart his plans.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">The goddess Velik looks at Manahan's memories and finds out that Shandra Manaya has been resurrected. The goddess Velik orders you to defeat Shandra Manaya before any more problems occur.&lt;BR&gt;You went to the Hall of the Argon Queen where you defeated Revivified Shandra Manaya, once again saving Arborea from doom.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3"
          huntingZoneId="3049"
          prevId="1"
          villagerId="1001">
        <Page social="0">If you put power into Manahan's Totem, you will be able to observe the moment when Agaia's power was used at its strongest.&lt;BR&gt;Are you ready to see Manahan's memories?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4"
          huntingZoneId="3049"
          prevId="3"
          villagerId="1001">
        <Page social="0">Shandra Manaya has been resurrected...&lt;BR&gt;Manahan seems to be doing all he can to get rid of Agaia's influence.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;If the seal of Agaia breaks, Arborea will once again be plunged into chaos like during the War of the Gods.&lt;BR&gt;You must defeat Shandra Manaya to prevent this disaster from taking its course in the first place. &lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Mysterious crystal?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">I sensed Karas' energy in the crystal.&lt;BR&gt;Some time has passed since Karas disappeared, but I'm glad that's he's still keeping Manahan in check.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;However, the fact that he himself is leaving a message is a bad omen.&lt;BR&gt;I need to ask you for help again. Defeat Shandra Manaya and stop Manahan.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Got it."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">I'll send you to Granarkus.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Let me know when you're ready.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5"
          huntingZoneId="50"
          prevId="4"
          villagerId="1036">
        <Page social="0">It surprised me that Shandra Manaya had been resurrected.&lt;BR&gt;It is clear that Manahan's power is growing stronger all the time.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Additionally, the uncertainty about the situation in the Hall of the Argon Queen is a big problem.&lt;BR&gt;Let's go inside and split up to find out more.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6"
          huntingZoneId="3055"
          prevId="5"
          villagerId="1101">
        <Page social="0">You defeated Shandra Manaya, &lt;PCNAME&gt;! I shouldn't be surprised though, considering your skills.&lt;BR&gt;Shandra Manaya's death has certainly foiled Manahan's plans. We can rest a little easier now.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;You nod.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Now that the situation is under control, you should report back to the goddess Velik.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Let me know when you're ready. I will send you directly to Velik's Sanctuary.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7"
          huntingZoneId="3049"
          prevId="6"
          villagerId="1001">
        <Page social="0">Greetings, &lt;PCNAME&gt;.&lt;BR&gt;I have sensed that Manahan's power has grown weaker.&lt;BR&gt;Did you defeat Shandra Manaya?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;You give your report.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Manahan won't be able to resurrect Shandra Manaya another time.&lt;BR&gt;However, I'm sure he won't back down so easily. We need to be on our guard. &lt;BR&gt;Besides, we still need to find out what that new power is that Karas was talking about. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Please continue to do your best for Arborea.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
