<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
             xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd"
             id="4"
             huntingZoneId="172"
             voiceTypeId="0"
             xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1"
          huntingZoneId="63"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="1532">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">We can depart once the recruits come back.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Zolyn doesn't like waiting. Could you pass on the message that the soldiers have completed their preparations?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">Dougal tells you the details of the mission. He is determined that this mission will be a success.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3"
          huntingZoneId="63"
          prevId="1"
          villagerId="1522">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">Hmph. &lt;PCNAME&gt;. I know your reputation. Nature reaps and you're her sickle.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I don't suppose you know Syona, the elin princess?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"I'm afraid not."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">No matter.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Well, you got our supplies squared away and our troopers back on their feet. That's more than the rest of these tuwangis can say!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Here's the sky cruiser's actuator. Dougal's waiting for it.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4"
          huntingZoneId="63"
          prevId="3"
          villagerId="1521">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">&lt;PCNAME&gt;! Good to have your courage by our side. Are you ready?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Ready when you are."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0"
              voiceTypeId="0">The actuator. Now we can finally leave. Excellent.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We're headed to Northern Arun. We believe the demokrons origin lies there…and a more personal mystery.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We'll talk more later.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5"
          huntingZoneId="63"
          prevId="4"
          villagerId="1521">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">Let's board now. I want to get under way.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Pyon will transport you to the ship when you're ready.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6"
          huntingZoneId="823"
          prevId="5"
          villagerId="1000">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">Welcome aboard! Isn't she magnificent? Larger than a sailing warship, capable of ferrying a full company of troops.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I'm not privy to all her secrets, but I know a lot of argon technology led to the sky cruisers.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7"
          huntingZoneId="823"
          villagerId="1000">
        <Page social="0">If you're ready, I'll show you to your cabin.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="8"
          huntingZoneId="823"
          prevId="6"
          villagerId="1005">
        <Page social="4"
              voiceTypeId="0">You saved Actol and I, &lt;PCNAME&gt;. Thank you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Don't worry; no more filching elixirs for us.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
