<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
             xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd"
             id="1"
             huntingZoneId="1"
             voiceTypeId="0"
             xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">&lt;PCNAME&gt;! &lt;BR&gt;There are argons in the Corrupted Skynest, as I'm sure you know. &lt;BR&gt;Until now, it was believed that argons only existed in Exodor, but I have also seen argons active in Arborea.&lt;BR&gt;Kaia has heard about this and is concerned that Arborea might be in danger. Visit me in the Kaiator Headquarters.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">Under orders from Kaia, you traveled to Castanica to search for the argons and gather information about the new power. There, you discovered that the barrier that had previously blocked access to Baldera no longer existed.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3"
          huntingZoneId="528"
          prevId="1"
          villagerId="10000">
        <Page social="0">Thanks for coming to see me so quickly, &lt;PCNAME&gt;.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We may have encountered argons in Exodor, but we believed Arborea to be a safe place. It turns out we were wrong.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"What happened?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">The argons in Arborea were deactivated after the war against Shandra Manaya.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;However, I have discovered that they are currently active again.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;As only a few argons are active, some believe they are faulty argons. However, many are inclined to think that the argons only move secretly when they're not being watched.&lt;BR&gt;That's what I think too.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Can they really be activated?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">I knew you'd ask that.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Watch. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I caught this argon near Castanica. It probably doesn't have very much energy left, that's why it isn't moving very much.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;But be careful! You never know when that might change.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4"
          huntingZoneId="528"
          prevId="3"
          villagerId="10020">
        <Page social="0">This argon kelba was caught by Hasmina.&lt;BR&gt;It barely moves, but its body is shaking a little. It has surely been activated.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5"
          huntingZoneId="528"
          prevId="4"
          villagerId="10030">
        <Page social="0">You are my sword.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;It's good to see you again. At the same time, I am sorry to have to impose a heavy burden on you.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Go on."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">I could even feel the shock from the core explosion in Exodor here in Arborea. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The shock destabilized the dimension.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I suspect it was this that led to the argons being reactivated.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;But I sense something other than the unstable dimension.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"What do you mean?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">The ancient power.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The power believed to be lost...&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The power originated somewhere in Castanica.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The argons must have been attracted to this power.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Be my sword and follow the power's trail.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6"
          huntingZoneId="528"
          prevId="5"
          villagerId="10010">
        <Page social="0">Did Kaia tell you everything?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We must go to Castanica to find the argons and the new power.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Hurry. Are you ready?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7"
          huntingZoneId="61"
          prevId="6"
          villagerId="10000">
        <Page social="0">It's been a long time since I came to Castanica.&lt;BR&gt;It hasn't changed much.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We should start by asking the residents whether they have any information about the argons.&lt;BR&gt;To the tavern on Pleasure Street! You'll hear all kinds of rumors from Arborea there.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Ah! We should take Rhodos with us. He pretty much lives in the tavern.&lt;BR&gt;Do you remember Rhodos? He's a Khirian captain.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="8"
          huntingZoneId="61"
          prevId="7"
          villagerId="1028">
        <Page social="0">Welcome.&lt;BR&gt;We have a new wine. It's very fresh and fruity. Would you like to try it?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Where's Rhodos?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Rhodos? Rhodos...&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Ah, the giant!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Hmm... I haven't seen him recently. He's usually here every day.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"What do you know about the argons?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Huh, you're interested in those dreadful things too?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Rumor has it that active argons have been running around before disappearing. But no one has really seen them.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Even Shade couldn't find them.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Who's Shade? Hmm... He's researching... some kind of animals? Or plants? Something along those lines.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;He was planning to leave today. He's on the second floor right now. You could speak to him if you like.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="9"
          huntingZoneId="61"
          prevId="8"
          villagerId="10020">
        <Page social="0">*cough* ... The argons have only recently appeared again.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;They don't travel in groups, but appear individually, watch, and then disappear.&lt;BR&gt;Why are you interested?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"I'm on a mission to search for the argons."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Any news?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Oh! Hey, &lt;PCCLASS&gt;!&lt;BR&gt;I teach ecology and am writing a paper on the argons in this regard.&lt;BR&gt;But I don't have enough data.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Take me along with you.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"But... it's bound to be exhausting for you."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">My knowledge of the argons will be extremely useful to you.&lt;BR&gt;Their characteristics, the way they fight, and their sociology... I know everything there is to know about them.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I'm also the foremost expert in the lifeforms and environment of Arborea.&lt;BR&gt;My knowledge will be invaluable to you. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;*cough*</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="10"
          huntingZoneId="61"
          prevId="9"
          villagerId="10021">
        <Page social="0">Hahaha! I knew it!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Not only does an adventurer need to be physically strong, but as intelligent as I am.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;*cough* When are you leaving?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"I'll set off now."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">You go on ahead and I'll catch up with you once I've packed my research tools. How about we meet later at the entrance to the Vexatus Swamp?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="11"
          huntingZoneId="61"
          prevId="10"
          villagerId="10003">
        <Page social="0">Kaia gave me this Faerie for you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;It will show you the right way.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="12"
          huntingZoneId="61"
          prevId="11"
          villagerId="20000">
        <Page social="0">Kaia's Faerie will show you the way.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Speak to Kaia's Faerie to find out more.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="13"
          huntingZoneId="3"
          prevId="12"
          villagerId="10000">
        <Page social="0">This is the place Kaia's Faerie led us to.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Wait... Doesn't this path led to Baldera?&lt;BR&gt;There definitely used to be a barrier up ahead.&lt;BR&gt;But now it's gone!&lt;BR&gt;That's why the Faerie brought us here.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
