<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
             xsi:schemaLocation="https://tera-arise.io/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd"
             id="23"
             huntingZoneId="1"
             voiceTypeId="0"
             xmlns="https://tera-arise.io/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">You are deeply saddened to break the sad news to Kaia.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2"
          huntingZoneId="0"
          prevId="0"
          villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">To honor the heroic deaths of Hasmina and Hellen, you returned to Allemantheia and attended the memorial service.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3"
          huntingZoneId="528"
          prevId="1"
          villagerId="10100">
        <Page social="0">It's heartbreaking.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The personalities that once shone like Arborea's stars are gradually disappearing.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Manahan is the cause of the pain and confusion that is spreading through Arborea. So many heroes have lost their lives for this!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;My sword, I know you're suffering too on account of the constant setbacks. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;But you mustn't give up.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You must shoulder this burden for the benefit of Arborea.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4"
          huntingZoneId="528"
          prevId="3"
          villagerId="10200">
        <Page social="0">Let's go to Allemantheia. After reporting to Fraya, we should say a prayer for Hasmina and Hellen.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5"
          huntingZoneId="518"
          prevId="4"
          villagerId="1001">
        <Page social="0">How can this be?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Hellen and Hasmina are... because of Dakuryon...&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The sisters have served Arborea diligently.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I will organize a memorial service to honor their actions.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Their achievements will be immortalized on the tombstone.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6"
          huntingZoneId="72"
          prevId="5"
          villagerId="40600">
        <Page social="0">You run your fingers gently over the tombstone.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You remember the good times and the bad, and her bravery when she charged towards enemies with her twin swords.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Hasmina's strength and willingness to fight for her comrades will live long in the memory.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7"
          huntingZoneId="72"
          prevId="6"
          villagerId="40900">
        <Page social="0">Hellen and Hasmina... Who could have imagined losing them in this senseless way.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We have been fighting Arborea's dangers for a long time, and we have lost many key figures along the way.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;And we may lose more in the future too. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;It could be me or another trusty comrade.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;But we must never give in. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Our mission is to keep the peace in Arborea, and we must do so at all costs.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
